For O
purposes O
of O
measuring O
impairment O
of O
those O
receivables O
" " O
an O
entity O
should O
apply O
the O
amendments O
prospectively O
for O
the O
first O
interim O
or O
annual O
period O
beginning O
on O
or O
after O
June O
15 O
" " O
2011 O
. O

The O
robust O
immune O
response O
coupled O
with O
improved O
survival O
relative O
to O
historical O
controls O
makes O
the O
data O
from O
this O
trial O
especially O
encouraging O
. O

Generally O
" " O
in O
any O
Plan O
year O
in O
which O
a O
participant O
does O
not O
receive O
the O
maximum O
Employer O
Matching O
Contribution O
to O
which O
he O
or O
she O
is O
entitled O
( O
due O
to O
periodic O
payroll-based O
limitations O
) O
" " O
the O
Employer O
will O
make O
a O
“ O
true-up O
” O
contribution O
( O
year-end O
reconciling O
Employer O
Matching O
Contribution O
) O
. O

Investments O
in O
securities O
traded O
on O
a O
national O
securities O
exchange O
or O
included O
in O
NASDAQ I-ORG
are O
generally O
valued O
at O
the O
last O
reported O
sales O
price O
" " O
the O
closing O
price O
or O
the O
official O
closing O
price O
; O
and O
securities O
traded O
in O
the O
over-the-counter O
market O
and O
listed O
securities O
for O
which O
no O
sale O
is O
reported O
on O
that O
date O
are O
valued O
at O
the O
last O
reported O
bid O
price O
. O

CORPORATE O
INFORMATION O
THE O
COMPANY O
Chemical I-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
is O
a O
registered O
financial O
holding O
company O
headquartered O
in O
Midland I-LOC
" " O
Michigan I-LOC
" " O
that O
operated O
through O
one O
commercial O
banking O
subsidiary O
" " O
Chemical I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
" " O
with O
129 O
banking O
offices O
in O
31 O
counties O
located O
generally O
across O
the O
mid- O
and O
lower-sections O
of O
Michigan I-LOC
's O
Lower I-LOC
Peninsula I-LOC
" " O
as O
of O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
. O

The O
Board O
of O
Directors O
has O
fixed O
the O
close O
of O
business O
on O
March O
5 O
" " O
2010 O
" " O
as O
the O
record O
date O
( O
the O
“ O
Record O
Date O
” O
) O
for O
the O
determination O
of O
Stockholders O
who O
are O
entitled O
to O
receive O
this O
Information O
Statement O
. O

THIS O
AGREEMENT O
" " O
as O
amended O
and O
restated O
effective O
as O
of O
the O
23rd O
day O
of O
June O
" " O
2011 O
" " O
by O
and O
between O
EMS I-ORG
TECHNOLOGIES I-ORG
" " I-ORG
INC. I-ORG
" " O
a O
Georgia I-LOC
corporation O
( O
the O
Company O
) O
" " O
and O
Gary I-PER
B I-PER
. I-PER
Shell I-PER
( O
the O
Executive O
) O
" " O
supersedes O
and O
replaces O
entirely O
any O
and O
all O
previous O
agreements O
between O
the O
Company O
and O
Executive O
that O
provides O
Executive O
with O
post-termination O
compensation O
" " O
following O
a O
change O
in O
the O
control O
of O
the O
Company O
" " O
of O
a O
nature O
or O
in O
amounts O
not O
otherwise O
provided O
under O
the O
terms O
of O
programs O
and O
policies O
applicable O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
employees O
generally O
. O

The O
more O
the O
Fund O
invests O
in O
leveraged O
instruments O
" " O
the O
more O
this O
leverage O
will O
magnify O
any O
losses O
on O
those O
investments O
. O

Distributions O
under O
a O
Section O
409A O
Award O
. O

-- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
S O
"2,500" O
"1,000" O
"1,000" O
"1,000" O
-- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
- O
-- O
-- O
- O

The O
price O
per O
share O
and O
aggregate O
offering O
price O
are O
calculated O
on O
the O
basis O
of O
the O
average O
of O
the O
high O
and O
low O
prices O
of O
the O
Registrant O
’ O
s O
common O
stock O
on O
June O
6 O
" " O
2011 O
" " O
as O
reported O
on O
the O
NASDAQ I-MISC
Global I-MISC
Market I-MISC
. O

Each O
element O
within O
a O
non-software O
multiple-element O
arrangement O
is O
accounted O
for O
as O
a O
separate O
unit O
of O
accounting O
provided O
the O
following O
criteria O
are O
met O
: O
the O
delivered O
services O
have O
value O
to O
the O
customer O
on O
a O
standalone O
basis O
; O
and O
for O
an O
arrangement O
that O
includes O
a O
general O
right O
of O
return O
relative O
to O
the O
delivered O
services O
" " O
delivery O
or O
performance O
of O
the O
undelivered O
service O
is O
considered O
probable O
and O
is O
substantially O
controlled O
by O
the O
Company O
. O

You O
are O
hereby O
notified O
that O
the O
2011 O
Annual O
Meeting O
of O
Stockholders O
( O
the O
Meeting O
) O
of O
Watson I-ORG
Pharmaceuticals I-ORG
" " I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
( O
the O
Company O
) O
will O
be O
held O
at O
Sheraton I-ORG
Parsippany I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
located O
at O
199 O
Smith I-LOC
Road I-LOC
" " O
Parsippany I-LOC
" " O
New I-LOC
Jersey I-LOC
at O
9:00 O
a.m. O
local O
time O
" " O
on O
May O
13 O
" " O
2011 O
" " O
for O
the O
following O
purposes O
: O

There O
can O
be O
no O
assurances O
that O
we O
will O
achieve O
our O
goal O
of O
profitable O
operations O
. O

The O
key O
functions O
of O
the O
Nominating O
and O
Corporate O
Governance O
Committee O
are O
to O
identify O
and O
present O
qualified O
candidates O
to O
the O
Board O
of O
Directors O
for O
election O
or O
re-election O
as O
directors O
of O
the O
Board O
and O
Board O
of O
Directors O
committees O
" " O
ensure O
that O
the O
size O
and O
composition O
of O
the O
Board O
of O
Directors O
" " O
its O
committees O
" " O
and O
our O
Charter O
and O
Bylaws O
are O
structured O
in O
a O
way O
that O
best O
serves O
our O
practices O
and O
objectives O
" " O
develop O
and O
recommend O
to O
the O
Board O
of O
Directors O
a O
set O
of O
corporate O
governance O
guidelines O
and O
principles O
and O
periodically O
review O
and O
recommend O
changes O
to O
such O
guidelines O
and O
principles O
as O
deemed O
appropriate O
" " O
and O
oversee O
the O
evaluation O
of O
the O
Board O
of O
Directors O
and O
senior O
management O
. O

Due O
to O
our O
lack O
of O
operating O
history O
and O
present O
inability O
to O
generate O
revenues O
" " O
however O
" " O
our O
auditors O
have O
stated O
their O
opinion O
that O
there O
currently O
exists O
substantial O
doubt O
about O
our O
ability O
to O
continue O
as O
a O
going O
concern O
. O

In O
order O
to O
approve O
the O
proposed O
Restated O
Plan O
: O
( O
i O
) O
greater O
than O
50 O
% O
in O
interest O
of O
all O
securities O
entitled O
to O
vote O
on O
the O
proposal O
must O
cast O
a O
vote O
on O
the O
proposal O
" " O
and O
( O
ii O
) O
a O
majority O
of O
such O
votes O
cast O
must O
vote O
for O
the O
Amendment O
. O

In O
this O
regard O
" " O
please O
advise O
us O
and O
revise O
future O
filings O
tell O
us O
how O
you O
determined O
that O
40 O
% O
was O
an O
appropriate O
discount O
factor O
for O
the O
control O
premium O
. O

Supplement O
to O
the O
Fidelity I-ORG
AdvisorSM I-ORG
Investment I-ORG
Grade I-ORG
Bond I-ORG
Fund I-ORG
Class O
A O
" " O
Class O
T O
" " O
Class O
B O
" " O
and O
Class O
C O
October O
30 O
" " O
2010 O
Prospectus O
The O
following O
information O
replaces O
similar O
information O
found O
under O
the O
heading O
`` O
Description I-MISC
of I-MISC
Principal I-MISC
Security I-MISC
Types I-MISC
'' O
in O
the O
`` O
Fund I-MISC
Basics I-MISC
'' O
section O
on O
page O
10 O
. O

Notwithstanding O
any O
other O
provision O
of O
the O
Plan O
" " O
the O
Plan O
" " O
and O
any O
Award O
granted O
or O
awarded O
to O
any O
individual O
who O
is O
then O
subject O
to O
Section O
16 O
of O
the O
Exchange I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
shall O
be O
subject O
to O
any O
additional O
limitations O
set O
forth O
in O
any O
applicable O
exemptive O
rule O
under O
Section O
16 O
of O
the O
Exchange I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
( O
including O
any O
amendment O
to O
Rule O
16b-3 O
of O
the O
Exchange I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
) O
that O
are O
requirements O
for O
the O
application O
of O
such O
exemptive O
rule O
. O

The O
Treasurer O
shall O
have O
the O
authority O
to O
invest O
the O
normal O
funds O
of O
the O
Corporation O
in O
the O
purchase O
and O
acquisition O
of O
investments O
and O
to O
sell O
and O
otherwise O
dispose O
of O
these O
investments O
upon O
such O
terms O
as O
the O
Treasurer O
may O
deem O
desirable O
and O
advantageous O
" " O
and O
shall O
" " O
upon O
request O
" " O
render O
to O
the O
President O
and O
the O
directors O
an O
accounting O
of O
all O
such O
normal O
investment O
transactions O
. O

As O
a O
result O
" " O
the O
compensation O
consultant O
s O
analysis O
did O
not O
include O
Mr. O
Cook I-PER
s O
February O
2010 O
study O
indicated O
that O
target O
compensation O
for O
our O
Named O
Executive O
Officers O
compared O
to O
the O
competitive O
range O
as O
shown O
in O
the O
following O
table O
: O

In O
addition O
" " O
at O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
" " O
there O
is O
approximately O
$ O
36 O
million O
and O
$ O
44 O
million O
" " O
respectively O
" " O
of O
unearned O
non-cash O
stock-based O
compensation O
related O
to O
performance-based O
options O
and O
RSUs O
that O
the O
Company O
could O
record O
as O
expense O
over O
a O
weighted O
average O
of O
3.1 O
and O
4.0 O
years O
" " O
respectively O
" " O
depending O
on O
the O
level O
of O
achievement O
of O
financial O
performance O
goals O
. O

Such O
defaults O
could O
result O
in O
losses O
to O
the O
Fund O
. O

Executive O
Vice O
Presidents O
" " O
Senior O
Vice O
Presidents O
" " O
Vice O
Presidents O
and O
Assistant O
Vice O
Presidents O
shall O
have O
duties O
and O
powers O
as O
the O
board O
of O
directors O
may O
designate O
. O

Tax O
Fees O
" " O
the O
aggregate O
fees O
billed O
in O
each O
of O
the O
last O
two O
fiscal O
years O
for O
professional O
services O
rendered O
by O
the O
principal O
accountant O
for O
tax O
compliance O
" " O
tax O
advice O
" " O
and O
tax O
planning O
are O
as O
follows O
: O

We O
hereby O
consent O
to O
the O
incorporation O
by O
reference O
in O
this O
Post-Effective O
Amendment O
No. O
1 O
to O
the O
Registration O
Statement O
on O
Form I-MISC
S-3 I-MISC
of O
Regency I-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Partners I-ORG
LP I-ORG
and O
Regency I-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Finance I-ORG
Corp. I-ORG
of O
our O
report O
dated O
February O
15 O
" " O
2011 O
relating O
to O
the O
financial O
statements O
of O
Midcontinent I-ORG
Express I-ORG
Pipeline I-ORG
LLC I-ORG
" " O
which O
appears O
in O
Regency I-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Partners I-ORG
LP I-ORG
s O
Annual O
Report O
on O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
for O
the O
year O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
. O

The O
other O
part O
of O
the O
process O
with O
the O
pending O
acquisition O
is O
filing O
an O
S-4 I-MISC
. O

During O
2011 O
" " O
the O
qualitative O
factors O
were O
reviewed O
and O
remained O
unchanged O
. O

Government O
legislation O
or O
regulation O
could O
affect O
the O
use O
of O
these O
transactions O
and O
could O
limit O
the O
fund O
's O
ability O
to O
pursue O
its O
investment O
strategies O
. O

The O
limited O
liability O
company O
agreement O
of O
Gulf I-ORG
States I-ORG
contains O
indemnification O
provisions O
that O
generally O
provide O
that O
Gulf I-ORG
States I-ORG
will O
indemnify O
any O
person O
against O
any O
losses O
" " O
damages O
" " O
claims O
or O
liabilities O
to O
which O
they O
may O
become O
subject O
or O
which O
Gulf I-ORG
States I-ORG
may O
incur O
as O
a O
result O
of O
being O
or O
having O
been O
a O
member O
" " O
director O
or O
officer O
of O
Gulf I-ORG
States I-ORG
or O
an O
officer O
" " O
director O
" " O
stockholder O
" " O
manager O
" " O
member O
or O
partner O
of O
Gulf I-ORG
States I-ORG
member O
" " O
or O
while O
serving O
in O
a O
similar O
capacity O
at O
the O
request O
of O
Gulf I-ORG
States I-ORG
" " O
and O
may O
advance O
to O
them O
or O
reimburse O
them O
for O
expenses O
incurred O
in O
connection O
therewith O
. O

For O
a O
Fund O
that O
provides O
annual O
total O
returns O
for O
only O
one O
calendar O
year O
or O
for O
a O
Fund O
that O
does O
not O
include O
the O
bar O
chart O
because O
it O
does O
not O
have O
annual O
returns O
for O
a O
full O
calendar O
year O
" " O
modify O
" " O
as O
appropriate O
" " O
the O
narrative O
explanation O
required O
by O
paragraph O
( O
c O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
( O
e.g. O
" " O
by O
stating O
that O
the O
information O
gives O
some O
indication O
of O
the O
risks O
of O
an O
investment O
in O
the O
Fund O
by O
comparing O
the O
Fund O
's O
performance O
with O
a O
broad O
measure O
of O
market O
performance O
) O
. O

The O
fund O
gains O
exposure O
to O
each O
asset O
class O
by O
investing O
primarily O
in O
a O
combination O
of O
Fidelity I-ORG
funds O
and O
unaffiliated O
ETFs O
( O
underlying O
funds O
) O
" " O
although O
it O
may O
also O
invest O
directly O
in O
individual O
securities O
. O

Beauty I-ORG
Brands I-ORG
Group I-ORG
" " I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
is O
a O
holding O
company O
that O
was O
incorporated O
in O
Florida I-LOC
in O
1968 O
. O

Such O
a O
trading O
halt O
near O
the O
time O
the O
Fund O
prices O
its O
shares O
may O
limit O
the O
Fund O
's O
ability O
to O
use O
leverage O
and O
may O
prevent O
the O
Fund O
from O
achieving O
its O
investment O
objective O
. O

The O
Barclays O
Capital O
Municipal O
Bond O
Index O
is O
considered O
representative O
of O
the O
broad O
market O
for O
investment-grade O
" " O
tax-exempt O
bonds O
with O
maturities O
of O
at O
least O
one O
year O
. O

We O
provide O
our O
Named O
Executive O
Officers O
with O
perquisites O
and O
other O
personal O
benefits O
that O
we O
and O
the O
Compensation O
Committee O
believe O
have O
a O
business O
purpose O
" " O
are O
reasonable O
and O
consistent O
with O
our O
overall O
compensation O
program O
and O
better O
enable O
us O
to O
attract O
and O
retain O
superior O
employees O
for O
key O
positions O
. O

Valuation O
allowances O
are O
recorded O
to O
reduce O
deferred O
tax O
assets O
when O
it O
is O
more O
likely O
than O
not O
that O
a O
tax O
benefit O
will O
not O
be O
realized O
. O

EXECUTIVE O
OFFICERS O
: O
David I-PER
B. I-PER
Ramaker I-PER
Chairman O
" " O
Chief O
Executive O
Officer O
and O
President O
Lori I-PER
A. I-PER
Gwizdala I-PER
Executive O
Vice O
President O
" " O
Chief O
Financial O
Officer O
and O
Corporate O
Treasurer O
Thomas I-PER
W. I-PER
Kohn I-PER
Executive O
Vice O
President O
of O
Community O
Banking O
and O
Corporate O
Secretary O
Kenneth I-PER
W. I-PER
Johnson I-PER
Executive O
Vice O
President O
and O
Director O
of O
Bank O
Operations O
John I-PER
E. I-PER
Kessler I-PER
Executive O
Vice O
President O
and O
Senior O
Trust O
Officer O
James I-PER
E. I-PER
Tomczyk I-PER
Executive O
Vice O
President O
and O
Senior O
Credit O
Officer O
Dominic I-PER
Monastiere I-PER
Executive O
Vice O
President O
and O
Chief O
Risk O
Management O
Officer O
Front O
Row O
Left O
to O
Right O
: O
Lori I-PER
A. I-PER
Gwizdala I-PER
" " O
David I-PER
B. I-PER
Ramaker I-PER
" " O
Thomas I-PER
W. I-PER
Kohn I-PER
Back O
Row O
Left O
to O
Right O
: O
Kenneth I-PER
W. I-PER
Johnson I-PER
" " O
John I-PER
E. I-PER
Kessler I-PER
" " O
James I-PER
E. I-PER
Tomczyk I-PER
" " O
Dominic I-PER
Monastiere I-PER
CORPORATE O
DIRECTORS O
: O
Gary I-PER
E. I-PER
Anderson I-PER
Lead O
Independent O
Director O
" " O
Chemical I-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
Retired O
Chairman O
" " O
Dow I-ORG
Corning I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
J. I-PER
Daniel I-PER
Bernson I-PER
Vice O
Chairman O
" " O
The I-ORG
Hanson I-ORG
Group I-ORG
Nancy I-PER
Bowman I-PER
Co-Owner O
" " O
Bowman I-ORG
& I-ORG
Rogers I-ORG
" " O
PC O
James I-PER
A. I-PER
Currie I-PER
Investor O
Thomas I-PER
T. I-PER
Huff I-PER
Attorney O
at O
Law O
" " O
Thoma I-PER
s I-PER
T. I-PER
Huff I-PER
" " O
PC O
Owner O
" " O
Peregrine I-ORG
Realty I-ORG
" " I-ORG
LLC I-ORG
and O
Peregrine I-ORG
Restaurant I-ORG
Group I-ORG
" " I-ORG
LLC I-ORG

As O
a O
shareholder O
of O
the O
Fund O
" " O
you O
incur O
two O
types O
of O
costs O
: O
( O
1 O
) O
transaction O
costs O
" " O
which O
may O
include O
sales O
charges O
( O
loads O
) O
on O
purchase O
payments O
and O
contingent O
deferred O
sales O
charges O
on O
redemptions O
and O
( O
2 O
) O
ongoing O
costs O
" " O
including O
management O
fees O
and O
other O
Fund O
expenses O
. O

Severability O
 O
If O
any O
provision O
of O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
be O
held O
invalid O
or O
unenforceable O
by O
any O
court O
of O
competent O
jurisdiction O
" " O
such O
holding O
shall O
not O
invalidate O
or O
render O
unenforceable O
any O
other O
provisions O
hereof O
. O

Pursuant O
to O
Rule O
12b-15 O
promulgated O
under O
the O
Securities I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Exchange I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
of I-LEGISLATION/ACT
1934 I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
filed O
with O
this O
Amendment O
is O
Exhibit O
13 O
with O
the O
corrected O
net O
income O
 O
basic O
of O
$ O
( O
0.44 O
) O
per O
share O
. O

Each O
director O
attended O
at O
least O
75 O
percent O
of O
the O
combined O
total O
of O
( O
i O
) O
all O
Board O
of O
Directors O
and O
( O
ii O
) O
all O
meetings O
of O
committees O
of O
which O
the O
director O
was O
a O
member O
. O

The O
Company O
's O
internal O
credit O
risk O
grading O
system O
is O
based O
on O
experiences O
with O
similarly O
graded O
loans O
. O

There O
will O
not O
be O
an O
increase O
or O
decrease O
in O
authorized O
shares O
nor O
will O
it O
affect O
the O
par O
value O
per O
share O
of O
the O
Company O
common O
stock O
. O

These O
lawsuits O
challenge O
certain O
policies O
and O
practices O
of O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
s O
credit O
card O
business O
. O

The O
appellate O
court O
directed O
the O
trial O
court O
to O
exercise O
its O
discretion O
to O
determine O
whether O
to O
grant O
leave O
to O
amend O
the O
complaint O
to O
add O
a O
new O
plaintiff O
. O

Please O
carefully O
consider O
the O
Risk O
Factors O
beginning O
on O
page O
4 O
of O
the O
accompanying O
Prospectus O
" " O
as O
well O
as O
the O
section O
entitled O
Risk O
Factors O
included O
in O
our O
recent O
quarterly O
and O
annual O
reports O
filed O
with O
the O
Securities I-GOVERNMENT
and I-GOVERNMENT
Exchange I-GOVERNMENT
Commission I-GOVERNMENT
. O

As O
reported O
on O
the O
supplemental O
schedule O
of O
delinquent O
participant O
contributions O
" " O
certain O
Plan O
contributions O
were O
not O
remitted O
to O
the O
Plan O
within O
the O
time O
frame O
specified O
by O
29 O
CFR I-LEGISLATION/ACT
2510-3-102 O
of O
the O
Department I-GOVERNMENT
of I-GOVERNMENT
Labor I-GOVERNMENT
’ O
s O
Rules O
and O
Regulations O
for O
reporting O
under O
ERISA I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
thus O
constituting O
nonexempt O
transactions O
between O
the O
Plan O
and O
Dover I-ORG
for O
the O
year O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
. O

For O
purposes O
of O
this O
Agreement O
" " O
termination O
or O
cessation O
of O
employment O
shall O
mean O
a O
separation O
from O
service O
within O
the O
meaning O
of O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
where O
it O
is O
reasonably O
anticipated O
that O
no O
further O
services O
would O
be O
performed O
after O
such O
date O
or O
that O
the O
level O
of O
bona O
fide O
services O
the O
Executive O
would O
perform O
after O
that O
date O
( O
whether O
as O
an O
employee O
or O
independent O
contractor O
) O
would O
permanently O
decrease O
to O
no O
more O
than O
20 O
% O
of O
the O
average O
level O
of O
bona O
fide O
services O
performed O
over O
the O
immediately O
preceding O
36-month O
period O
( O
or O
" " O
if O
lesser O
" " O
Executive O
s O
period O
of O
service O
) O
. O

as O
of O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
and O
2009 O
" " O
and O
the O
related O
consolidated O
statements O
of O
income O
" " O
cash O
flows O
" " O
and O
partners O
capital O
for O
the O
year O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
and O
for O
the O
period O
from O
March O
18 O
" " O
2009 O
to O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
" " O
and O
the O
related O
statements O
of O
income O
" " O
cash O
flows O
" " O
and O
member O
s O
interest O
of O
Regency I-ORG
Intrastate I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
LLC I-ORG
for O
the O
period O
from O
January O
1 O
" " O
2009 O
to O
March O
17 O
" " O
2009 O
" " O
incorporated O
herein O
by O
reference O
. O

Derivative O
instruments O
may O
be O
difficult O
to O
value O
" " O
may O
be O
illiquid O
" " O
and O
may O
be O
subject O
to O
wide O
swings O
in O
valuation O
caused O
by O
changes O
in O
the O
value O
of O
the O
underlying O
instrument O
. O

When O
a O
fund O
does O
not O
already O
own O
or O
have O
the O
right O
to O
obtain O
securities O
equivalent O
in O
kind O
and O
amount O
" " O
a O
commitment O
to O
sell O
securities O
is O
equivalent O
to O
a O
short O
sale O
. O

In O
addition O
" " O
in O
2010 O
directors O
were O
paid O
$ O
"2,000" O
for O
each O
Board O
of O
Directors O
meeting O
personally O
attended O
and O
$ O
"1,000" O
for O
each O
meeting O
attended O
telephonically O
. O

Furthermore O
" " O
if O
any O
of O
these O
units O
fail O
to O
achieve O
expected O
performance O
levels O
or O
experience O
a O
downturn O
in O
the O
business O
below O
current O
expectations O
" " O
goodwill O
could O
be O
impaired O
. O

As O
of O
the O
end O
of O
the O
period O
covered O
by O
this O
report O
( O
the O
“ O
Evaluation O
Date O
” O
) O
" " O
the O
Company O
carried O
out O
an O
evaluation O
" " O
under O
the O
supervision O
and O
with O
the O
participation O
of O
the O
Company O
’ O
s O
Principal O
Executive O
Officer O
and O
Principal O
Financial O
Officer O
( O
the O
“ O
Certifying O
Officers O
” O
) O
of O
the O
effectiveness O
of O
the O
design O
and O
operation O
of O
the O
Company O
’ O
s O
disclosure O
controls O
and O
procedures O
( O
as O
defined O
in O
rules O
13a-15 O
( O
e O
) O
and O
15d-15 O
( O
e O
) O
) O
under O
the O
Exchange I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

We O
believe O
that O
" " O
because O
the O
Company O
does O
not O
offer O
a O
defined O
benefit O
pension O
plan O
" " O
such O
a O
deferred O
compensation O
arrangement O
should O
be O
included O
as O
a O
component O
of O
a O
market O
competitive O
compensation O
program O
to O
assist O
participants O
in O
planning O
and O
saving O
for O
their O
retirement O
. O

( O
i O
) O
No O
Award O
under O
the O
Plan O
may O
be O
sold O
" " O
pledged O
" " O
assigned O
or O
transferred O
in O
any O
manner O
other O
than O
by O
will O
or O
the O
laws O
of O
descent O
and O
distribution O
or O
" " O
subject O
to O
the O
consent O
of O
the O
Administrator O
" " O
pursuant O
to O
a O
DRO O
" " O
unless O
and O
until O
such O
Award O
has O
been O
exercised O
" " O
or O
the O
shares O
underlying O
such O
Award O
have O
been O
issued O
" " O
and O
all O
restrictions O
applicable O
to O
such O
shares O
have O
lapsed O
; O

At O
March O
31 O
" " O
2011 O
the O
risk O
factors O
of O
the O
Company O
have O
not O
changed O
materially O
from O
those O
reported O
in O
our O
Annual O
Report O
on O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

The O
adoption O
of O
this O
guidance O
by O
the O
Plan O
resulted O
in O
the O
reclassification O
from O
investments O
to O
notes O
receivable O
from O
participants O
of O
$ O
"27,478" O
on O
the O
Statement O
of O
Net O
Assets O
Available O
for O
Benefits O
as O
of O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
. O

The O
table O
compares O
the O
Fund O
's O
returns O
for O
each O
period O
with O
those O
of O
the O
FTSE I-MISC
National I-MISC
Association I-MISC
of I-MISC
Real I-MISC
Estate I-MISC
Investment I-MISC
Trusts I-MISC
( I-MISC
NAREIT I-MISC
) I-MISC
Equity I-MISC
REITs I-MISC
Index I-MISC
" " O
which O
reflects O
performance O
of O
all O
publicly O
traded O
equity O
REITs O
other O
than O
those O
designated O
as O
timber O
REITs O
" " O
and O
its O
former O
benchmark O
" " O
FTSE I-MISC
NAREIT I-MISC
All I-MISC
Equity I-MISC
REITs I-MISC
Index I-MISC
" " O
which O
reflects O
performance O
of O
all O
publicly O
traded O
equity O
REITs O
" " O
including O
timber O
REITs O
. O

The O
following O
tables O
present O
the O
financial O
position O
" " O
results O
of O
operations O
and O
cash O
flows O
of O
SunGard I-ORG
( O
referred O
to O
as O
Parent O
Company O
for O
purposes O
of O
this O
note O
only O
) O
" " O
the O
Guarantor O
subsidiaries O
" " O
the O
Non-Guarantor O
subsidiaries O
and O
Eliminations O
as O
of O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
and O
2010 O
" " O
and O
for O
the O
years O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2008 O
" " O
2009 O
and O
2010 O
to O
arrive O
at O
the O
information O
for O
SunGard I-ORG
on O
a O
consolidated O
basis O
. O

Such O
list O
shall O
be O
open O
to O
the O
examination O
of O
any O
stockholder O
" " O
for O
any O
purpose O
germane O
to O
the O
meeting O
" " O
during O
ordinary O
business O
hours O
" " O
for O
a O
period O
of O
at O
least O
ten O
days O
prior O
to O
the O
meeting O
" " O
either O
at O
a O
place O
within O
the O
city O
or O
other O
municipality O
or O
community O
where O
the O
meeting O
is O
to O
be O
held O
" " O
which O
place O
shall O
be O
specified O
in O
the O
notice O
of O
the O
meeting O
" " O
or O
if O
not O
so O
specified O
" " O
at O
the O
place O
where O
the O
meeting O
is O
to O
be O
held O
. O

( O
b O
) O
Notwithstanding O
anything O
in O
the O
Plan O
to O
the O
contrary O
" " O
the O
Committee O
may O
grant O
any O
Award O
to O
a O
Section O
162 O
( O
m O
) O
Participant O
" " O
including O
a O
Restricted O
Stock O
award O
" " O
a O
Restricted O
Stock O
Unit O
award O
" " O
a O
Dividend O
Equivalent O
award O
" " O
a O
Deferred O
Stock O
award O
or O
a O
Stock O
Payment O
award O
" " O
the O
restrictions O
with O
respect O
to O
which O
lapse O
upon O
the O
attainment O
of O
performance O
goals O
which O
are O
related O
to O
one O
or O
more O
of O
the O
Performance O
Criteria O
and O
any O
Award O
described O
in O
Article O
VIII O
that O
vests O
or O
becomes O
exercisable O
or O
payable O
upon O
the O
attainment O
of O
performance O
goals O
which O
are O
related O
to O
one O
or O
more O
of O
the O
Performance O
Criteria O
. O

A O
copy O
of O
this O
Form I-MISC
8-K I-MISC
is O
included O
in O
this O
Prospectus O
Supplement O
No. O
This O
Prospectus O
Supplement O
No. O
5 O
should O
be O
read O
in O
conjunction O
with O
" " O
and O
delivered O
with O
" " O
the O
Prospectus O
and O
is O
qualified O
by O
reference O
to O
the O
Prospectus O
except O
to O
the O
extent O
that O
the O
information O
in O
this O
Prospectus O
Supplement O
No. O
5 O
supersedes O
the O
information O
contained O
in O
the O
Prospectus O
. O

The O
target O
number O
of O
restricted O
shares O
to O
be O
awarded O
to O
a O
Named O
Executive O
Officer O
s O
under O
a O
Performance O
Award O
is O
equal O
to O
his O
or O
her O
actual O
Time O
Share O
award O
granted O
in O
the O
fiscal O
year O
for O
which O
performance O
is O
being O
measured O
. O

( O
Applicable O
only O
to O
Class O
A O
purchases O
after O
October O
23 O
" " O
2009 O
) O
Purchased O
by O
a O
shareholder O
who O
redeemed O
Destiny I-MISC
Plan I-MISC
assets O
and O
received O
the O
proceeds O
in O
the O
form O
of O
directly O
held O
shares O
of O
a O
Fidelity I-ORG
Advisor I-ORG
fund I-ORG
after O
September O
30 O
" " O
2008 O
. O

Purchased O
by O
a O
charitable O
organization O
( O
as O
defined O
for O
purposes O
of O
Section O
501 O
( O
c O
) O
( O
3 O
) O
of O
the O
Internal I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Revenue I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Code I-LEGISLATION/ACT
) O
or O
a O
charitable O
remainder O
trust O
or O
life O
income O
pool O
established O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
a O
charitable O
organization O
; O

Our O
responsibility O
is O
to O
express O
an O
opinion O
on O
the O
Company O
s O
compliance O
based O
on O
our O
examination O
. O

The O
Company O
s O
remaining O
10 O
reporting O
units O
" " O
whose O
goodwill O
balances O
in O
aggregate O
total O
$ O
3.2 O
billion O
as O
of O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
" " O
each O
had O
estimated O
fair O
values O
in O
excess O
of O
25 O
% O
more O
than O
the O
carrying O
value O
of O
the O
reporting O
unit O
as O
of O
the O
July O
1 O
" " O
2010 O
impairment O
test O
. O

The O
number O
of O
shares O
of O
Deferred O
Stock O
shall O
be O
determined O
by O
the O
Administrator O
and O
may O
be O
based O
upon O
the O
Performance O
Criteria O
or O
other O
specific O
performance O
criteria O
determined O
to O
be O
appropriate O
by O
the O
Administrator O
" " O
in O
each O
case O
on O
a O
specified O
date O
or O
dates O
or O
over O
any O
period O
or O
periods O
determined O
by O
the O
Administrator O
. O

This O
Example O
is O
intended O
to O
help O
you O
compare O
the O
cost O
of O
investing O
in O
the O
fund O
with O
the O
cost O
of O
investing O
in O
other O
mutual O
funds O
. O

The O
Chief O
Executive O
Officer O
shall O
be O
the O
head O
of O
the O
Corporation O
and O
shall O
have O
general O
and O
active O
supervision O
of O
the O
business O
of O
the O
Corporation O
and O
shall O
see O
that O
all O
orders O
and O
resolutions O
of O
the O
board O
of O
directors O
are O
carried O
into O
effect O
and O
shall O
be O
responsible O
to O
the O
board O
of O
directors O
for O
the O
execution O
of O
such O
duties O
and O
powers O
. O

The O
Subsidiary O
is O
managed O
by O
FMRC I-ORG
and O
has O
the O
same O
investment O
objective O
as O
the O
fund O
. O

Revenues O
in O
the O
third O
fiscal O
quarter O
are O
expected O
to O
be O
in O
the O
range O
of O
$ O
34.0 O
million O
to O
$ O
36.0 O
million O
. O

We O
pay O
a O
stream O
of O
fixed O
interest O
payments O
for O
the O
term O
of O
the O
swap O
" " O
and O
in O
turn O
" " O
receive O
variable O
interest O
payments O
based O
on O
one-month O
LIBOR O
or O
three-month O
LIBOR O
( O
0.26 O
% O
and O
0.30 O
% O
" " O
respectively O
" " O
at O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
) O
. O

Also O
" " O
the O
following O
discussion O
includes O
historical O
and O
certain O
forward-looking O
information O
that O
should O
be O
read O
together O
with O
the O
accompanying O
Consolidated O
Financial O
Statements O
and O
related O
footnotes O
and O
the O
discussion O
above O
of O
certain O
risks O
and O
uncertainties O
( O
see O
ITEM O
1ARISK O
FACTORS O
) O
that O
could O
cause O
future O
operating O
results O
to O
differ O
materially O
from O
historical O
results O
or O
the O
expected O
results O
indicated O
by O
forward-looking O
statements O
. O

At O
March O
31 O
" " O
2011 O
and O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
" " O
there O
were O
no O
loans O
considered O
to O
be O
impaired O
. O

Termination O
of O
Directorship O
shall O
mean O
the O
time O
when O
a O
Holder O
who O
is O
an O
Independent O
Director O
ceases O
to O
be O
a O
Director O
for O
any O
reason O
" " O
including O
" " O
but O
not O
by O
way O
of O
limitation O
" " O
a O
termination O
by O
resignation O
" " O
removal O
" " O
failure O
to O
be O
elected O
" " O
death O
or O
retirement O
. O

Under O
normal O
circumstances O
" " O
the O
fund O
invests O
at O
least O
80 O
% O
of O
net O
assets O
" " O
plus O
the O
amount O
of O
any O
borrowings O
for O
investment O
purposes O
" " O
in O
securities O
backed O
by O
the O
full O
faith O
and O
credit O
of O
the O
US O
government O
" " O
including O
related O
repurchase O
agreements O
( O
the O
`` O
80 O
% O
test O
'' O
) O
. O

The O
Assistant O
Secretary O
" " O
or O
if O
there O
be O
more O
than O
one O
" " O
the O
Assistant O
Secretaries O
in O
the O
order O
determined O
by O
the O
board O
of O
directors O
" " O
shall O
" " O
in O
the O
absence O
or O
disability O
of O
the O
Secretary O
" " O
perform O
the O
duties O
and O
exercise O
the O
powers O
of O
the O
Secretary O
and O
shall O
perform O
such O
other O
duties O
and O
have O
such O
other O
powers O
as O
the O
board O
of O
directors O
may O
from O
time O
to O
time O
prescribe O
. O

We O
Are O
Not O
Required O
to O
Meet O
or O
Maintain O
Any O
Listing O
Standards O
for O
Our O
Common O
Stock O
to O
Be O
Quoted O
on O
the O
OTC I-MISC
Bulletin I-MISC
Board I-MISC
" " O
Which O
Could O
Affect O
Our O
Stockholders O
’ O
Ability O
to O
Access O
Trading O
Information O
about O
Our O
Common O
Stock O
. O

IN O
WITNESS O
WHEREOF O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
caused O
this O
Agreement O
to O
be O
executed O
on O
its O
behalf O
by O
its O
duly O
authorized O
officers O
and O
the O
Executive O
has O
hereunder O
set O
his O
or O
her O
hand O
" " O
as O
of O
the O
date O
first O
above O
written O
. O

The O
Company O
expects O
to O
reclassify O
in O
the O
next O
twelve O
months O
approximately O
$ O
33 O
million O
of O
expense O
from O
accumulated O
other O
comprehensive O
income O
into O
earnings O
related O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
interest O
rate O
swaps O
based O
on O
the O
borrowing O
rates O
at O
December O
31 O
" " O
2010 O
. O

