-DOCSTART- O

Item O
5.02 O
Departure O
of O
Directors O
or O
Certain O
Officers O
; O
Election O
of O
Directors O
; O
Appointment O
of O
Certain O
Officers O
; O
Compensatory O
Arrangements O
of O
Certain O
Officers O
. O

On O
June O
23 O
" " O
2011 O
" " O
EMS I-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
" " I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
( O
the O
Company O
) O
and O
Gary I-PER
B I-PER
. I-PER
Shell I-PER
" " O
the O
Company O
s O
Senior O
Vice O
President O
" " O
Chief O
Financial O
Officer O
and O
Treasurer O
" " O
entered O
into O
an O
Amended O
and O
Restated O
Executive O
Protection O
Agreement O
( O
the O
Amended O
EPA O
) O
. O

The O
Amended O
EPA O
includes O
a O
new O
non-compete O
provision O
that O
prohibits O
Mr. O
Shell I-PER
from O
competing O
with O
the O
Company O
for O
six O
months O
following O
a O
termination O
of O
his O
employment O
for O
any O
reason O
. O

In O
connection O
with O
the O
addition O
of O
the O
non-compete O
" " O
the O
Amended O
EPA O
allocates O
$ O
"75,000" O
of O
any O
payments O
ultimately O
paid O
to O
Mr. O
Shell I-PER
under O
the O
Amended O
EPA O
as O
consideration O
for O
the O
non-compete O
. O

EMS I-ORG
TECHNOLOGIES I-ORG
" " I-ORG
INC. I-ORG

THIS O
AGREEMENT O
" " O
as O
amended O
and O
restated O
effective O
as O
of O
the O
23rd O
day O
of O
June O
" " O
2011 O
" " O
by O
and O
between O
EMS I-ORG
TECHNOLOGIES I-ORG
" " I-ORG
INC. I-ORG
" " O
a O
Georgia I-LOC
corporation O
( O
the O
Company O
) O
" " O
and O
Gary I-PER
B I-PER
. I-PER
Shell I-PER
( O
the O
Executive O
) O
" " O
supersedes O
and O
replaces O
entirely O
any O
and O
all O
previous O
agreements O
between O
the O
Company O
and O
Executive O
that O
provides O
Executive O
with O
post-termination O
compensation O
" " O
following O
a O
change O
in O
the O
control O
of O
the O
Company O
" " O
of O
a O
nature O
or O
in O
amounts O
not O
otherwise O
provided O
under O
the O
terms O
of O
programs O
and O
policies O
applicable O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
employees O
generally O
. O

WHEREAS O
" " O
the O
Company O
wishes O
to O
assure O
both O
itself O
and O
its O
key O
employees O
of O
continuity O
of O
management O
and O
objective O
judgment O
in O
the O
event O
of O
any O
Change O
in O
Control O
( O
as O
defined O
below O
) O
of O
the O
Company O
and O
to O
provide O
certain O
other O
benefits O
" " O
and O
the O
Executive O
is O
a O
key O
employee O
of O
the O
Company O
and O
an O
integral O
part O
of O
its O
management O
; O
NOW O
" " O
THEREFORE O
" " O
for O
and O
in O
consideration O
of O
the O
premises O
and O
the O
mutual O
covenants O
herein O
contained O
" " O
the O
parties O
hereby O
agree O
as O
follows O
: O

I O
. O
TERM O
OF O
AGREEMENT O
. O

This O
Agreement O
shall O
be O
effective O
immediately O
upon O
its O
execution O
by O
the O
parties O
hereto O
. O

The O
term O
of O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
be O
for O
a O
rolling O
" " O
three-year O
period O
commencing O
on O
the O
date O
hereof O
" " O
and O
shall O
be O
deemed O
automatically O
( O
without O
further O
action O
by O
either O
the O
Company O
or O
the O
Executive O
) O
to O
extend O
each O
day O
for O
an O
additional O
day O
such O
that O
the O
remaining O
term O
of O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
continue O
to O
be O
three O
years O
. O

The O
foregoing O
notwithstanding O
" " O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
immediately O
cease O
to O
be O
effective O
and O
shall O
terminate O
if O
the O
Executive O
ceases O
to O
be O
employed O
by O
the O
Company O
" " O
at O
any O
time O
before O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
( O
as O
defined O
below O
) O
has O
occurred O
" " O
in O
a O
corporate O
officer O
position O
of O
vice O
president O
or O
higher O
position O
; O
provided O
" " O
however O
" " O
such O
cessation O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
employment O
( O
i O
) O
was O
not O
at O
the O
request O
of O
a O
third O
party O
who O
has O
indicated O
an O
intention O
or O
taken O
steps O
reasonably O
calculated O
to O
effect O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
" " O
( O
ii O
) O
did O
not O
otherwise O
occur O
in O
connection O
with O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
that O
in O
fact O
occurs O
" " O
or O
( O
iii O
) O
did O
not O
occur O
in O
connection O
with O
a O
Board-authorized O
plan O
for O
" " O
or O
Board-authorized O
implementation O
efforts O
with O
respect O
to O
" " O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
( O
whether O
or O
not O
such O
Change O
in O
Control O
in O
fact O
occurs O
) O
. O

Board O
— O
The O
Board O
of O
Directors O
of O
the O
Company O
" " O
or O
its O
successor O
. O

Cause O
— O
The O
term O
Cause O
as O
used O
herein O
shall O
mean O
: O
( O
i O
) O
any O
act O
that O
constitutes O
" " O
on O
the O
part O
of O
the O
Executive O
" " O
( O
a O
) O
fraud O
" " O
dishonesty O
" " O
gross O
negligence O
" " O
or O
willful O
misconduct O
and O
( O
b O
) O
that O
directly O
results O
in O
material O
injury O
to O
the O
Company O
" " O
or O
( O
ii O
) O
the O
Executive O
s O
conviction O
of O
a O
felony O
or O
crime O
involving O
moral O
turpitude O
. O

events O
or O
circumstances O
constituting O
Cause O
to O
the O
reasonable O
satisfaction O
of O
the O
Company O
. O

A O
termination O
for O
Cause O
based O
on O
clause O
( O
ii O
) O
above O
shall O
take O
effect O
immediately O
upon O
giving O
of O
the O
termination O
notice O
. O

Change O
in O
Control O
— O
The O
term O
Change O
in O
Control O
as O
used O
herein O
shall O
mean O
the O
occurrence O
of O
one O
of O
the O
following O
: O

( O
iv O
) O
the O
occurrence O
of O
any O
other O
event O
or O
circumstance O
which O
is O
not O
covered O
by O
( O
i O
) O
through O
( O
iii O
) O
above O
which O
the O
Board O
determines O
affects O
control O
of O
the O
Company O
and O
constitutes O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
for O
purposes O
of O
this O
Agreement O
. O

Disability O
— O
The O
term O
Disability O
shall O
mean O
the O
Executive O
s O
inability O
as O
a O
result O
of O
physical O
or O
mental O
incapacity O
to O
substantially O
perform O
his O
or O
her O
duties O
for O
the O
Company O
on O
a O
full-time O
basis O
for O
a O
period O
of O
six O
months O
. O

Excess O
Severance O
Payment O
— O
The O
term O
Excess O
Severance O
Payment O
shall O
have O
the O
same O
meaning O
as O
the O
term O
excess O
parachute O
payment O
defined O
in O
Section O
280G O
( O
b O
) O
( O
l O
) O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

Severance O
Payment O
— O
The O
term O
Severance O
Payment O
shall O
have O
the O
same O
meaning O
as O
the O
term O
parachute O
payment O
defined O
in O
Section O
280G O
( O
b O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

Present O
Value O
— O
The O
term O
Present O
Value O
shall O
have O
the O
same O
meaning O
as O
provided O
in O
Section O
280G O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

Reasonable O
Compensation O
— O
The O
term O
Reasonable O
Compensation O
shall O
have O
the O
same O
meaning O
as O
provided O
in O
Section O
280G O
( O
b O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

BENEFITS O
UPON O
TERMINATION O
. O

( O
ii O
) O
on O
or O
within O
24 O
months O
after O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
" " O
and O
such O
termination O
is O
a O
result O
of O
Involuntary O
Termination O
or O
Voluntary O
Termination O
" " O
as O
defined O
below O
" " O

then O
the O
benefits O
described O
in O
Section O
2 O
below O
shall O
" " O
subject O
to O
Article O
IV O
of O
this O
Agreement O
" " O
be O
paid O
or O
provided O
to O
the O
Executive O
. O

The O
fact O
that O
Executive O
is O
eligible O
for O
early O
" " O
normal O
or O
delayed O
retirement O
under O
a O
Company O
retirement O
plan O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
or O
her O
termination O
shall O
not O
make O
him O
or O
her O
ineligible O
to O
receive O
benefits O
hereunder O
. O

For O
the O
purposes O
of O
the O
following O
definitions O
" " O
the O
term O
Company O
shall O
include O
the O
Company O
s O
subsidiaries O
and O
any O
successor O
as O
a O
result O
of O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
to O
the O
business O
and O
assets O
of O
the O
Company O
or O
its O
subsidiaries O
. O

( O
a O
) O
Involuntary O
Termination O
— O
For O
purposes O
hereof O
" " O
Involuntary O
Termination O
shall O
mean O
termination O
of O
employment O
that O
is O
involuntary O
on O
the O
part O
of O
the O
Executive O
and O
that O
occurs O
for O
reasons O
other O
than O
Cause O
" " O
Disability O
or O
death O
. O

( O
b O
) O
Voluntary O
Termination O
— O
For O
purposes O
hereof O
" " O
Voluntary O
Termination O
shall O
mean O
termination O
of O
employment O
that O
is O
voluntary O
on O
the O
part O
of O
the O
Executive O
" " O
and O
" " O
in O
the O
judgment O
of O
the O
Executive O
" " O
is O
due O
to O
" " O
and O
which O
occurs O
within O
six O
months O
of O
: O

( O
i O
) O
the O
assignment O
to O
the O
Executive O
of O
any O
duties O
inconsistent O
with O
the O
Executive O
s O
title O
and O
status O
in O
effect O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
" " O
a O
material O
increase O
or O
decrease O
in O
the O
Executive O
s O
responsibilities O
at O
the O
Company O
from O
those O
in O
effect O
immediately O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
" " O
or O
an O
adverse O
alteration O
in O
the O
nature O
or O
status O
of O
such O
responsibilities O
( O
other O
than O
any O
such O
alteration O
to O
the O
extent O
incidental O
to O
the O
fact O
that O
the O
Company O
may O
no O
longer O
be O
a O
public O
company O
) O
; O

( O
ii O
) O
a O
reduction O
by O
the O
Company O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
base O
salary O
from O
such O
salary O
in O
effect O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
; O

the O
year O
preceding O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
) O
" " O
except O
for O
required O
travel O
on O
the O
Company O
s O
business O
to O
an O
extent O
substantially O
consistent O
with O
the O
Executive O
s O
business O
travel O
obligations O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
; O

( O
iv O
) O
the O
failure O
by O
the O
Company O
" " O
without O
the O
Executive O
s O
consent O
" " O
to O
pay O
to O
the O
Executive O
any O
portion O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
then-current O
compensation O
( O
including O
base O
salary O
and O
annual O
bonus O
to O
the O
extent O
payable O
under O
the O
terms O
of O
annual O
bonus O
programs O
in O
effect O
from O
time O
to O
time O
) O
" " O
or O
to O
pay O
to O
the O
Executive O
any O
portion O
of O
an O
installment O
of O
deferred O
compensation O
under O
any O
deferred O
compensation O
program O
of O
the O
Company O
" " O
in O
each O
case O
within O
seven O
days O
of O
the O
date O
such O
compensation O
is O
due O
; O

( O
v O
) O
the O
failure O
by O
the O
Company O
to O
continue O
in O
effect O
any O
compensation O
plan O
in O
which O
the O
Executive O
participates O
immediately O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
" " O
which O
is O
material O
to O
the O
Executive O
s O
total O
compensation O
" " O
including O
but O
not O
limited O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
annual O
bonus O
plan O
" " O
stock O
option O
plan O
" " O
or O
any O
similar O
or O
substitute O
plans O
adopted O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
" " O
unless O
an O
equitable O
arrangement O
( O
embodied O
in O
an O
ongoing O
substitute O
or O
alternative O
plan O
) O
has O
been O
made O
with O
respect O
to O
such O
plan O
" " O
or O
the O
failure O
by O
the O
Company O
to O
continue O
the O
Executive O
s O
participation O
in O
such O
plan O
( O
or O
in O
such O
substitute O
or O
alternative O
plan O
) O
on O
a O
basis O
not O
materially O
less O
favorable O
" " O
both O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
amount O
of O
benefits O
provided O
( O
or O
potentially O
available O
under O
incentive O
compensation O
programs O
) O
and O
the O
level O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
participation O
relative O
to O
other O
participants O
" " O
as O
existed O
immediately O
prior O
to O
the O
Change O
in O
Control O
; O

( O
vii O
) O
the O
failure O
of O
any O
successor O
to O
assume O
this O
Agreement O
as O
provided O
in O
Section O
V.2 O
below O
. O

A O
termination O
shall O
not O
be O
considered O
voluntary O
within O
the O
meaning O
of O
this O
Agreement O
if O
such O
termination O
is O
the O
result O
of O
Cause O
" " O
Disability O
or O
death O
of O
the O
Executive O
. O

The O
Executive O
s O
continued O
employment O
shall O
not O
constitute O
consent O
to O
" " O
or O
a O
waiver O
of O
rights O
with O
respect O
to O
" " O
any O
act O
or O
failure O
to O
act O
relating O
to O
Voluntary O
Termination O
hereunder O
. O

Benefits O
to O
be O
Provided O
— O
If O
the O
Executive O
becomes O
eligible O
for O
benefits O
under O
Section O
1 O
above O
" " O
the O
Company O
shall O
pay O
or O
provide O
to O
the O
Executive O
the O
compensation O
and O
benefits O
set O
forth O
in O
this O
Section O
2 O
. O

( O
a O
) O
Salary O
— O
The O
Executive O
will O
continue O
to O
receive O
his O
or O
her O
current O
salary O
( O
subject O
to O
withholding O
of O
all O
applicable O
taxes O
and O
any O
amounts O
referred O
to O
in O
Section O
2 O
( O
b O
) O
below O
) O
for O
the O
period O
specified O
below O
following O
his O
date O
of O
termination O
in O
the O
same O
manner O
as O
it O
was O
being O
paid O
as O
of O
the O
date O
of O
termination O
; O
provided O
" " O
however O
" " O
that O
the O
salary O
payments O
provided O
for O
hereunder O
shall O
be O
paid O
in O
a O
single O
lump O
sum O
payment O
" " O
to O
be O
paid O
not O
earlier O
than O
six O
months O
and O
one O
day O
" " O
and O
not O
later O
than O
seven O
months O
" " O
after O
his O
or O
her O
termination O
of O
employment O
; O
provided O
" " O
further O
" " O
that O
the O
amount O
of O
such O
lump O
sum O
payment O
shall O
be O
determined O
by O
taking O
the O
salary O
payments O
to O
be O
made O
and O
discounting O
them O
to O
their O
Present O
Value O
on O
the O
date O
the O
Executive O
s O
employment O
is O
terminated O
" " O
increased O
by O
interest O
on O
such O
amount O
for O
each O
day O
from O
the O
31st O
day O
after O
termination O
of O
employment O
until O
the O
date O
of O
payment O
" " O
calculated O
on O
a O
daily O
basis O
at O
a O
rate O
per O
annum O
equal O
to O
the O
rate O
used O
to O
determine O
such O
Present O
Value O
. O

For O
purposes O
hereof O
" " O
the O
Executive O
s O
current O
salary O
shall O
be O
the O
highest O
rate O
in O
effect O
during O
the O
six-month O
period O
prior O
to O
the O
Executive O
s O
termination O
. O

The O
period O
for O
which O
such O
salary O
payments O
shall O
be O
so O
made O
shall O
be O
as O
follows O
: O

( O
ii O
) O
24 O
months O
in O
the O
case O
of O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
occurring O
with O
the O
prior O
approval O
of O
the O
Board O
of O
Directors O
. O

( O
b O
) O
Health O
and O
Life O
Insurance O
Coverage O
— O
The O
health O
and O
life O
insurance O
benefits O
coverage O
( O
including O
any O
executive O
medical O
plan O
or O
split O
dollar O
insurance O
plan O
) O
provided O
to O
the O
Executive O
at O
his O
or O
her O
date O
of O
termination O
( O
or O
" " O
if O
greater O
" " O
within O
six O
months O
prior O
to O
such O
date O
of O
termination O
) O
" " O
shall O
be O
provided O
by O
the O
Company O
( O
no O
less O
frequently O
than O
monthly O
) O
at O
its O
expense O
at O
the O
same O
level O
and O
in O
the O
same O
manner O
as O
if O
his O
or O
her O
employment O
had O
not O
terminated O
( O
and O
" " O
if O
applicable O
" " O
such O
coverage O
had O
not O
been O
terminated O
or O
modified O
within O
six O
months O
prior O
to O
such O
date O
of O
termination O
) O
" " O
but O
subject O
to O
the O
customary O
changes O
in O
such O
coverages O
if O
the O
Executive O
reaches O
age O
65 O
or O
has O
similar O
changes O
in O
personal O
or O
family O
circumstances O
" " O
beginning O
on O
the O
date O
of O
such O
termination O
and O
ending O
on O
the O
date O
12 O
months O
from O
the O
date O
of O
such O
termination O
. O

Any O
additional O
coverages O
the O
Executive O
had O
at O
termination O
" " O
including O
dependent O
coverage O
" " O
will O
also O
be O
continued O
for O
such O
period O
on O
the O
same O
terms O
" " O
to O
the O
extent O
permitted O
by O
the O
applicable O
policies O
or O
contracts O
. O

Any O
costs O
the O
Executive O
was O
paying O
for O
such O
coverages O
at O
the O
time O
of O
termination O
shall O
be O
paid O
by O
the O
Executive O
by O
separate O
check O
payable O
to O
the O
Company O
each O
month O
in O
advance O
. O

the O
terms O
of O
any O
benefit O
plan O
as O
described O
above O
. O

The O
coverages O
provided O
for O
in O
this O
subsection O
shall O
be O
applied O
against O
and O
reduce O
the O
period O
for O
which O
COBRA I-LEGISLATION/ACT
will O
be O
provided O
" " O
and O
may O
at O
the O
Company O
s O
election O
be O
provided O
as O
COBRA I-LEGISLATION/ACT
coverage O
" " O
subject O
to O
payment O
by O
the O
Company O
to O
the O
Executive O
( O
monthly O
in O
advance O
) O
of O
additional O
compensation O
equal O
to O
the O
excess O
of O
the O
COBRA I-LEGISLATION/ACT
premium O
over O
the O
costs O
otherwise O
payable O
by O
the O
Executive O
as O
provided O
above O
" " O
in O
each O
case O
as O
in O
effect O
from O
time O
to O
time O
" " O
plus O
an O
additional O
amount O
as O
necessary O
to O
reimburse O
the O
Executive O
for O
additional O
taxes O
payable O
on O
both O
such O
additional O
compensation O
and O
such O
additional O
amount O
at O
a O
combined O
tax O
rate O
of O
45 O
% O
; O
provided O
" " O
however O
" " O
that O
the O
first O
of O
any O
such O
payments O
by O
the O
Company O
shall O
be O
made O
no O
earlier O
than O
six O
months O
and O
one O
day O
" " O
and O
not O
later O
than O
seven O
months O
" " O
after O
the O
Executive O
s O
termination O
of O
employment O
and O
shall O
include O
all O
amounts O
so O
payable O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
first O
seven O
months O
following O
such O
termination O
. O

( O
c O
) O
Stock O
Options O
— O
As O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
date O
of O
termination O
" " O
all O
outstanding O
stock O
options O
granted O
to O
the O
Executive O
under O
any O
stock O
option O
plan O
or O
program O
maintained O
by O
the O
Company O
shall O
become O
100 O
% O
vested O
and O
immediately O
exercisable O
" " O
and O
shall O
thereafter O
remain O
exercisable O
until O
the O
expiration O
dates O
otherwise O
in O
effect O
had O
the O
Executive O
remained O
continuously O
employed O
by O
the O
Company O
. O

( O
d O
) O
Annual O
Bonus O
for O
the O
Year O
Preceding O
Termination O
— O
If O
not O
previously O
paid O
" " O
the O
Company O
shall O
pay O
to O
the O
Executive O
cash O
incentive O
compensation O
for O
the O
year O
preceding O
the O
year O
in O
which O
the O
termination O
occurs O
" " O
in O
an O
amount O
determined O
in O
accordance O
with O
" " O
and O
payable O
as O
provided O
in O
" " O
the O
Company O
s O
Executive O
Annual O
Incentive O
Compensation O
Plan O
( O
or O
successor O
or O
replacement O
plan O
) O
as O
in O
effect O
for O
such O
preceding O
year O
. O

( O
e O
) O
Annual O
Bonus O
for O
the O
Year O
of O
Termination O
— O
In O
the O
case O
of O
a O
Change O
in O
Control O
occurring O
with O
the O
prior O
approval O
of O
the O
Board O
of O
Directors O
" " O
the O
Company O
shall O
pay O
to O
the O
Executive O
cash O
incentive O
compensation O
for O
the O
year O
in O
which O
the O
termination O
occurs O
in O
the O
amount O
determined O
in O
accordance O
with O
" " O
and O
payable O
as O
provided O
in O
" " O
the O
Company O
s O
Executive O
Annual O
Incentive O
Compensation O
Plan O
( O
or O
successor O
or O
replacement O
plan O
) O
as O
in O
effect O
for O
such O
year O
. O

( O
f O
) O
Effect O
of O
Death O
— O
In O
the O
event O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
death O
after O
he O
becomes O
entitled O
to O
payments O
or O
benefits O
hereunder O
" " O
the O
payments O
and O
benefits O
shall O
be O
continued O
to O
his O
or O
her O
spouse O
for O
the O
remainder O
of O
the O
applicable O
36- O
" " O
24- O
or O
12-month O
period O
. O

If O
the O
Executive O
is O
not O
married O
" " O
the O
payments O
and O
benefits O
shall O
cease O
on O
his O
or O
her O
date O
of O
death O
. O

( O
g O
) O
Allocation O
for O
Non-Competition O
Obligation O
. O

— O
A O
portion O
of O
the O
payments O
paid O
to O
Executive O
under O
this O
Agreement O
in O
the O
amount O
of O
$ O
"75,000" O
is O
paid O
to O
Executive O
as O
consideration O
for O
Executive O
s O
Non-Competition O
Obligation O
under O
Article O
VII O
of O
this O
Agreement O
. O

LIMITATION O
OF O
BENEFITS O
. O

Limitation O
of O
Amount O
— O
Notwithstanding O
anything O
in O
this O
Agreement O
to O
the O
contrary O
" " O
if O
any O
of O
the O
compensation O
or O
benefits O
payable O
" " O
or O
to O
be O
provided O
" " O
to O
the O
Executive O
by O
the O
Company O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
are O
treated O
as O
Excess O
Severance O
Payments O
( O
whether O
alone O
or O
in O
conjunction O
with O
payments O
or O
benefits O
outside O
of O
this O
Agreement O
) O
" " O
the O
compensation O
and O
benefits O
provided O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
shall O
be O
modified O
or O
reduced O
in O
the O
manner O
provided O
in O
Section O
2 O
below O
to O
the O
extent O
necessary O
so O
that O
the O
compensation O
and O
benefits O
payable O
or O
to O
be O
provided O
to O
the O
Executive O
under O
this O
Agreement O
that O
are O
treated O
as O
Severance O
Payments O
" " O
as O
well O
as O
any O
compensation O
or O
benefits O
provided O
outside O
of O
this O
Agreement O
that O
are O
so O
treated O
" " O
shall O
not O
cause O
the O
Company O
to O
have O
paid O
an O
Excess O
Severance O
Payment O
. O

In O
computing O
such O
amount O
" " O
the O
parties O
shall O
take O
into O
account O
all O
provisions O
of O
Code O
Section O
280G O
" " O
and O
the O
regulations O
thereunder O
" " O
including O
making O
appropriate O
adjustments O
to O
such O
calculation O
for O
amounts O
established O
to O
be O
Reasonable O
Compensation O
" " O
and O
for O
amounts O
paid O
to O
the O
Executive O
as O
consideration O
for O
the O
Executive O
s O
Non-Competition O
Obligation O
under O
Article O
VII O
of O
this O
Agreement O
. O

The O
determinations O
under O
this O
Section O
IV.1 O
with O
regard O
to O
Excess O
Severance O
Payments O
shall O
be O
made O
by O
an O
independent O
accounting O
firm O
selected O
by O
the O
Company O
and O
the O
Executive O
" " O
which O
shall O
provide O
detailed O
supporting O
calculations O
to O
the O
parties O
. O

Modification O
of O
Amount O
— O
In O
the O
event O
that O
the O
amount O
of O
any O
Severance O
Payments O
which O
would O
be O
payable O
to O
or O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
the O
Executive O
under O
this O
Agreement O
must O
be O
modified O
or O
reduced O
to O
comply O
with O
this O
Article O
" " O
the O
Executive O
shall O
direct O
which O
Severance O
Payments O
are O
to O
be O
modified O
or O
reduced O
but O
only O
to O
the O
extent O
that O
the O
right O
to O
direct O
" " O
and O
the O
actual O
direction O
of O
" " O
which O
Severance O
Payments O
are O
to O
be O
modified O
or O
reduced O
does O
not O
result O
in O
any O
failure O
of O
this O
Agreement O
to O
comply O
with O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

If O
the O
right O
to O
direct O
" " O
or O
the O
actual O
direction O
of O
" " O
which O
Severance O
Payments O
are O
to O
be O
modified O
or O
reduced O
would O
result O
in O
any O
failure O
of O
this O
Agreement O
or O
any O
other O
arrangement O
to O
comply O
with O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
" " O
then O
" " O
in O
lieu O
of O
the O
Executive O
s O
right O
to O
direct O
which O
Severance O
Payments O
are O
to O
be O
reduced O
or O
modified O
" " O
the O
order O
of O
reduction O
" " O
on O
a O
pro O
rata O
basis O
within O
each O
category O
" " O
shall O
be O
first O
any O
such O
cash O
payments O
" " O
next O
any O
equity O
compensation O
" " O
then O
any O
medical O
or O
life O
insurance O
and O
lastly O
any O
other O
remaining O
payments O
or O
benefits O
. O

No O
increase O
in O
the O
amount O
of O
any O
payment O
shall O
be O
made O
without O
the O
consent O
of O
the O
Company O
. O

Avoidance O
of O
Penalty O
Taxes O
— O
This O
Article O
shall O
be O
interpreted O
so O
as O
to O
avoid O
the O
imposition O
of O
excise O
taxes O
on O
the O
Executive O
under O
Section O
4999 O
of O
the O
Code O
or O
the O
disallowance O
of O
a O
deduction O
to O
the O
Company O
pursuant O
to O
Section O
280G O
( O
a O
) O
of O
the O
Code O
with O
respect O
to O
amounts O
payable O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
. O

In O
connection O
with O
any O
Internal I-GOVERNMENT
Revenue I-GOVERNMENT
Service I-GOVERNMENT
examination O
" " O
audit O
or O
other O
inquiry O
" " O
the O
Company O
and O
the O
Executive O
agree O
to O
take O
action O
to O
provide O
" " O
and O
to O
cooperate O
in O
providing O
" " O
evidence O
to O
the O
Internal I-GOVERNMENT
Revenue I-GOVERNMENT
Service I-GOVERNMENT
that O
the O
compensation O
and O
benefits O
provided O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
do O
not O
result O
in O
the O
payment O
of O
Excess O
Severance O
Payments O
. O

Additional O
Limitation O
— O
In O
addition O
to O
the O
limits O
otherwise O
provided O
in O
this O
Article O
" " O
to O
the O
extent O
permitted O
by O
law O
the O
Executive O
may O
in O
his O
or O
her O
sole O
discretion O
elect O
to O
reduce O
( O
or O
change O
the O
timing O
of O
) O
any O
payments O
he O
may O
be O
eligible O
to O
receive O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
to O
prevent O
the O
imposition O
of O
excise O
taxes O
on O
the O
Executive O
under O
Section O
4999 O
of O
the O
Code O
or O
to O
otherwise O
reduce O
or O
delay O
liability O
for O
taxes O
owed O
under O
the O
Code O
; O
but O
" " O

only O
if O
the O
right O
of O
the O
Executive O
to O
elect O
to O
reduce O
( O
or O
change O
the O
timing O
of O
) O
any O
payments O
he O
or O
she O
may O
be O
eligible O
to O
receive O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
" " O
or O
any O
actual O
election O
to O
reduce O
( O
or O
change O
the O
timing O
of O
) O
any O
payments O
he O
or O
she O
may O
be O
eligible O
to O
receive O
under O
this O
Agreement O
or O
otherwise O
" " O
will O
not O
result O
in O
any O
failure O
of O
this O
Agreement O
or O
other O
arrangement O
to O
comply O
with O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

Notices O
— O
Any O
notice O
to O
a O
party O
required O
or O
permitted O
to O
be O
given O
hereunder O
shall O
be O
in O
writing O
and O
shall O
be O
deemed O
given O
when O
delivered O
and O
shall O
be O
hand O
delivered O
" " O
sent O
by O
facsimile O
transmission O
with O
request O
for O
confirmation O
of O
receipt O
" " O
or O
mailed O
registered O
or O
certified O
mail O
( O
return O
receipt O
requested O
) O
" " O
to O
such O
party O
at O
such O
party O
s O
address O
as O
specified O
below O
" " O
or O
at O
such O
other O
address O
as O
such O
party O
shall O
specify O
by O
notice O
to O
the O
other O
. O

If O
to O
the O
Executive O
" " O
to O
his O
or O
her O
last O
address O
provided O
to O
the O
Company O
by O
the O
Executive O
" " O
and O
if O
none O
as O
otherwise O
shown O
on O
the O
records O
of O
the O
Company O
. O

Assignment O
— O
This O
Agreement O
shall O
inure O
to O
the O
benefit O
of O
and O
shall O
be O
binding O
upon O
the O
parties O
hereto O
and O
their O
respective O
executors O
" " O
administrators O
" " O
heirs O
" " O
personal O
representatives O
and O
successors O
" " O
but O
" " O
except O
as O
hereinafter O
provided O
" " O
neither O
this O
Agreement O
nor O
any O
right O
hereunder O
may O
be O
assigned O
or O
transferred O
by O
either O
party O
thereto O
" " O
or O
by O
any O
beneficiary O
or O
any O
other O
person O
" " O
nor O
be O
subject O
to O
alienation O
" " O
anticipation O
" " O
sale O
" " O
pledge O
" " O
encumbrance O
" " O
execution O
" " O
levy O
or O
other O
legal O
process O
of O
any O
kind O
against O
the O
Executive O
" " O
his O
or O
her O
beneficiary O
or O
any O
other O
person O
. O

Notwithstanding O
the O
foregoing O
" " O
any O
person O
or O
business O
entity O
succeeding O
to O
substantially O
all O
of O
the O
business O
of O
the O
Company O
by O
purchase O
" " O
merger O
" " O
consolidation O
" " O
sale O
of O
assets O
or O
otherwise O
" " O
shall O
be O
bound O
by O
this O
Agreement O
and O
must O
assume O
all O
obligations O
of O
the O
Company O
set O
forth O
in O
this O
Agreement O
" " O
and O
the O
Company O
shall O
use O
its O
reasonable O
best O
efforts O
to O
obtain O
such O
assumption O
prior O
to O
the O
effective O
date O
of O
any O
such O
succession O
. O

No O
Obligation O
to O
Fund O
— O
The O
agreement O
of O
the O
Company O
( O
or O
its O
successor O
) O
to O
make O
payments O
to O
the O
Executive O
hereunder O
shall O
represent O
solely O
the O
unsecured O
obligation O
of O
the O
Company O
( O
and O
its O
successor O
) O
" " O
except O
to O
the O
extent O
the O
Company O
( O
or O
its O
successor O
) O
in O
its O
sole O
discretion O
elects O
in O
whole O
or O
in O
part O
to O
fund O
its O
obligations O
under O
this O
Agreement O
pursuant O
to O
a O
trust O
arrangement O
or O
otherwise O
. O

Arbitration O
of O
Disputes O
; O
Expenses O
— O
All O
claims O
by O
the O
Executive O
for O
compensation O
and O
benefits O
under O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
be O
directed O
to O
and O
determined O
by O
the O
Board O
and O
shall O
be O
in O
writing O
. O

submission O
of O
such O
claim O
" " O
and O
shall O
set O
forth O
the O
specific O
reasons O
for O
the O
denial O
and O
the O
specific O
provisions O
of O
this O
Agreement O
relied O
upon O
. O

Any O
further O
dispute O
or O
controversy O
arising O
under O
or O
in O
connection O
with O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
be O
settled O
exclusively O
by O
arbitration O
in O
Atlanta I-LOC
" " O
Georgia I-LOC
" " O
in O
accordance O
with O
the O
commercial O
arbitration O
rules O
of O
the O
American I-ORG
Arbitration I-ORG
Association I-ORG
then O
in O
effect O
. O

The O
arbitration O
award O
shall O
be O
final O
and O
binding O
upon O
the O
parties O
" " O
and O
judgment O
upon O
the O
award O
may O
be O
entered O
on O
the O
arbitrator O
s O
award O
in O
any O
court O
having O
jurisdiction O
. O

Any O
arbitration O
award O
in O
favor O
of O
the O
Executive O
" " O
in O
whole O
or O
in O
part O
" " O
shall O
include O
interest O
" " O
at O
the O
rate O
of O
10 O
% O
per O
annum O
" " O
on O
the O
amount O
awarded O
from O
the O
date O
it O
was O
due O
for O
payment O
as O
provided O
in O
this O
Agreement O
. O

In O
the O
event O
the O
Executive O
incurs O
legal O
fees O
and O
other O
expenses O
in O
seeking O
to O
obtain O
or O
enforce O
any O
rights O
or O
benefits O
provided O
by O
this O
Agreement O
and O
is O
successful O
" " O
in O
whole O
or O
in O
part O
" " O
in O
obtaining O
or O
enforcing O
any O
such O
rights O
or O
benefits O
through O
settlement O
" " O
arbitration O
or O
otherwise O
" " O
the O
Company O
shall O
pay O
" " O
and O
any O
arbitration O
award O
shall O
include O
" " O
the O
Executive O
s O
reasonable O
legal O
fees O
and O
expenses O
incurred O
in O
enforcing O
this O
Agreement O
and O
the O
Executive O
s O
share O
of O
the O
fees O
of O
the O
arbitrator O
" " O
such O
fees O
and O
expenses O
to O
be O
paid O
by O
the O
Company O
promptly O
but O
in O
any O
event O
within O
30 O
days O
after O
any O
final O
settlement O
" " O
arbitration O
or O
adjudication O
of O
any O
denial O
of O
claim O
for O
benefits O
hereunder O
. O

Except O
to O
the O
extent O
provided O
in O
the O
preceding O
sentence O
" " O
each O
party O
shall O
pay O
its O
own O
legal O
fees O
and O
other O
expenses O
associated O
with O
any O
dispute O
" " O
provided O
" " O
that O
the O
fee O
for O
the O
arbitrator O
shall O
be O
shared O
equally O
. O

Amendment O
— O
This O
Agreement O
may O
only O
be O
amended O
by O
a O
written O
instrument O
signed O
by O
the O
parties O
hereto O
" " O
which O
makes O
specific O
reference O
to O
this O
Agreement O
. O

Severability O
— O
If O
any O
provision O
of O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
be O
held O
invalid O
or O
unenforceable O
by O
any O
court O
of O
competent O
jurisdiction O
" " O
such O
holding O
shall O
not O
invalidate O
or O
render O
unenforceable O
any O
other O
provisions O
hereof O
. O

Other O
Benefits O
— O
Nothing O
in O
this O
Agreement O
shall O
limit O
or O
replace O
the O
compensation O
or O
benefits O
payable O
to O
the O
Executive O
" " O
or O
otherwise O
adversely O
affect O
the O
Executive O
s O
rights O
" " O
under O
any O
other O
benefit O
plan O
" " O
program O
or O
agreement O
to O
which O
the O
Executive O
is O
a O
party O
. O

SECTION O
409A O
COMPLIANCE O
. O

Notwithstanding O
any O
other O
provision O
of O
this O
Agreement O
to O
the O
contrary O
" " O
it O
is O
intended O
that O
any O
payment O
or O
benefit O
provided O
pursuant O
to O
or O
in O
connection O
with O
this O
Agreement O
that O
is O
considered O
to O
be O
nonqualified O
deferred O
compensation O
subject O
to O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
shall O
be O
provided O
and O
paid O
in O
a O
manner O
" " O
and O
at O
such O
time O
" " O
including O
without O
limitation O
payment O
and O
provision O
of O
benefits O
only O
in O
connection O
with O
the O
occurrence O
of O
a O
permissible O
payment O
event O
contained O
in O
Section O
409A O
" " O
that O
complies O
with O
the O
applicable O
requirements O
of O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
" " O
to O
avoid O
the O
unfavorable O
tax O
consequences O
provided O
therein O
for O
non-compliance O
. O

For O
purposes O
of O
this O
Agreement O
" " O
all O
rights O
to O
payments O
and O
benefits O
hereunder O
shall O
be O
treated O
as O
rights O
to O
receive O
a O
series O
of O
separate O
payments O
and O
benefits O
to O
the O
fullest O
extent O
allowed O
by O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
. O

required O
by O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
( O
the O
409A O
deferral O
period O
) O
. O

In O
the O
event O
such O
payments O
are O
otherwise O
due O
to O
be O
made O
during O
the O
409A O
deferral O
period O
" " O
the O
payments O
which O
would O
otherwise O
have O
been O
made O
in O
the O
409A O
deferral O
period O
shall O
be O
accumulated O
and O
paid O
in O
a O
lump O
sum O
as O
soon O
as O
the O
409A O
deferral O
period O
ends O
" " O
and O
the O
balance O
of O
the O
payments O
shall O
be O
made O
as O
otherwise O
scheduled O
. O

In O
the O
event O
benefits O
are O
required O
to O
be O
deferred O
" " O
any O
such O
benefit O
may O
be O
provided O
during O
the O
409A O
deferral O
period O
at O
the O
Executive O
s O
expense O
" " O
with O
the O
Executive O
having O
the O
right O
to O
reimbursement O
from O
the O
Company O
once O
the O
409A O
deferral O
period O
ends O
" " O
and O
the O
balance O
of O
the O
benefits O
shall O
be O
provided O
as O
otherwise O
scheduled O
. O

For O
purposes O
of O
this O
Agreement O
" " O
termination O
or O
cessation O
of O
employment O
shall O
mean O
a O
separation O
from O
service O
within O
the O
meaning O
of O
Section O
409A O
of O
the O
Code O
where O
it O
is O
reasonably O
anticipated O
that O
no O
further O
services O
would O
be O
performed O
after O
such O
date O
or O
that O
the O
level O
of O
bona O
fide O
services O
the O
Executive O
would O
perform O
after O
that O
date O
( O
whether O
as O
an O
employee O
or O
independent O
contractor O
) O
would O
permanently O
decrease O
to O
no O
more O
than O
20 O
% O
of O
the O
average O
level O
of O
bona O
fide O
services O
performed O
over O
the O
immediately O
preceding O
36-month O
period O
( O
or O
" " O
if O
lesser O
" " O
Executive O
s O
period O
of O
service O
) O
. O

NON-COMPETITION O
OBLIGATION O
For O
a O
period O
of O
six O
( O
6 O
) O
months O
following O
Executive O
s O
termination O
of O
employment O
for O
any O
reason O
" " O
Executive O
shall O
not O
( O
a O
) O
organize O
or O
form O
any O
other O
business O
that O
will O
compete O
with O
the O
Business O
of O
the O
Company O
( O
as O
defined O
below O
) O
or O
( O
b O
) O
engage O
in O
the O
executive O
management O
of O
" " O
or O
provide O
consulting O
services O
concerning O
the O
executive O
management O
of O
" " O
any O
person O
or O
business O
entity O
that O
competes O
with O
the O
Business O
of O
the O
Company O
" " O
other O
than O
the O
Company O
or O
its O
affiliates O
within O
the O
Territory O
. O

The O
term O
Business O
of O
the O
Company O
means O
the O
design O
" " O
development O
" " O
manufacturing O
" " O
sale O
and O
provision O
of O
wireless O
connectivity O
solutions O
addressing O
the O
enterprise O
mobility O
" " O
communications-on-the-move O
" " O
tracking O
and O
in-flight O
connectivity O
markets O
for O
commercial O
and O
government O
users O
" " O
including O
but O
not O
limited O
to O
: O

The O
design O
" " O
development O
" " O
manufacturing O
" " O
sale O
and O
provision O
of O
( O
a O
) O
satellite-based O
communications O
through O
a O
broad O
array O
of O
terminals O
and O
antennas O
for O
the O
aeronautical O
markets O
and O
( O
b O
) O
in-cabin O
connection O
devices O
and O
computers O
to O
process O
data O
on O
board O
aircraft O
" " O
including O
rugged O
data O
storage O
" " O
airborne O
connectivity O
" " O
air-to-ground O
connectivity O
" " O
and O
data O
recording O
and O
replay O
equipment O
; O

( O
ii O
) O
Defense O
and O
Space O
. O

The O
design O
" " O
development O
" " O
manufacturing O
" " O
sale O
and O
provision O
of O
antenna O
and O
radio O
frequency O
beam O
management O
systems O
for O
a O
broad O
range O
of O
military O
and O
commercial O
applications O
" " O
including O
mobile O
network-centric O
operations O
" " O
RADAR O
for O
battlefield O
visibility O
and O
precision O
strike O
" " O
satellite O
sub-system O
" " O
and O
commercial O
aero O
connectivity O
; O

( O
iv O
) O
Global O
Tracking O
. O

The O
design O
" " O
development O
" " O
manufacturing O
" " O
sale O
and O
provision O
of O
satellite-based O
communication O
products O
and O
services O
for O
telematics O
and O
micro O
telemetry O
applications O
into O
global O
markets O
" " O
including O
those O
which O
enable O
customers O
to O
locate O
" " O
track O
" " O
communicate O
" " O
and O
safeguard O
mobile O
assets O
" " O
fleets O
" " O
cargo O
and O
personnel O
" " O
as O
well O
as O
to O
monitor O
fixed O
assets O
in O
hostile O
and O
remote O
terrains O
. O

The O
term O
Territory O
means O
the O
territory O
for O
which O
Executive O
is O
providing O
services O
at O
the O
time O
of O
termination O
of O
Executive O
s O
employment O
. O

Executive O
acknowledges O
and O
agrees O
that O
the O
Territory O
identified O
in O
this O
Article O
VII O
is O
an O
area O
for O
which O
Executive O
performs O
services O
for O
the O
Company O
by O
being O
actively O
engaged O
as O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Company O
s O
executive O
management O
team O
. O

Executive O
agrees O
that O
Executive O
s O
obligations O
under O
this O
Article O
VII O
are O
obligations O
which O
will O
continue O
beyond O
the O
date O
Executive O
s O
employment O
terminates O
and O
that O
such O
obligations O
are O
reasonable O
and O
necessary O
to O
protect O
the O
Company O
s O
legitimate O
business O
interests O
. O

Executive O
agrees O
that O
the O
remedies O
at O
law O
available O
to O
the O
Company O
for O
any O
actual O
or O
threatened O
breach O
by O
Executive O
of O
the O
covenants O
in O
this O
Article O
VII O
would O
be O
inadequate O
and O
that O
the O
Company O
shall O
be O
entitled O
to O
specific O
performance O
of O
the O
covenants O
in O
this O
Article O
VII O
" " O
including O
entry O
of O
an O
ex O
parte O
" " O
temporary O
restraining O
order O
in O
state O
or O
federal O
court O
" " O
preliminary O
and O
permanent O
injunctive O
relief O
against O
activities O
in O
violation O
of O
this O
Article O
VII O
" " O
or O
both O
" " O
or O
other O
appropriate O
judicial O
remedy O
" " O
writ O
or O
order O
" " O
in O
addition O
to O
any O
damages O
and O
legal O
expenses O
which O
the O
Company O
may O
be O
legally O
entitled O
to O
recover O
without O
the O
purchase O
and O
posting O
of O
bond O
or O
other O
security O
. O

IN O
WITNESS O
WHEREOF O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
caused O
this O
Agreement O
to O
be O
executed O
on O
its O
behalf O
by O
its O
duly O
authorized O
officers O
and O
the O
Executive O
has O
hereunder O
set O
his O
or O
her O
hand O
" " O
as O
of O
the O
date O
first O
above O
written O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
( O
Mark O
One O
) O

Indicate O
by O
check O
mark O
if O
the O
registrant O
is O
a O
well-known O
seasoned O
issuer O
" " O
as O
defined O
in O
Rule O
405 O
of O
the O
Securities I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

Yes O
No O
x O
Indicate O
by O
check O
mark O
if O
the O
registrant O
is O
not O
required O
to O
file O
reports O
pursuant O
to O
Section O
13 O
or O
15 O
( O
d O
) O
of O
the O
Act O
. O

Yes O
x O
No O
Indicate O
by O
check O
mark O
if O
disclosure O
of O
delinquent O
filers O
pursuant O
to O
Item O
405 O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
S-K I-LEGISLATION/ACT
is O
not O
contained O
herein O
" " O
and O
will O
not O
be O
contained O
" " O
to O
the O
best O
of O
registrant O
s O
knowledge O
" " O
in O
definitive O
proxy O
or O
information O
statements O
incorporated O
by O
reference O
in O
Part O
III O
of O
this O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
or O
any O
amendment O
to O
this O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

Yes O
No O
x O
State O
the O
aggregate O
market O
value O
of O
the O
voting O
and O
non-voting O
common O
equity O
held O
by O
nonaffiliates O
computed O
by O
reference O
to O
the O
price O
at O
which O
the O
common O
equity O
was O
last O
sold O
" " O
or O
the O
average O
bid O
and O
asked O
prices O
of O
such O
common O
equity O
" " O
as O
of O
the O
last O
business O
day O
of O
the O
registrant O
s O
most O
recently O
completed O
second O
fiscal O
quarter O
. O

The O
registrant O
had O
no O
voting O
or O
non-voting O
common O
equity O
outstanding O
as O
of O
the O
last O
business O
day O
of O
the O
registrant O
s O
most O
recently O
completed O
second O
fiscal O
quarter O
or O
the O
date O
of O
this O
report O
. O

The O
following O
Items O
have O
been O
omitted O
in O
accordance O
with O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
: O

Substitute O
information O
provided O
in O
accordance O
with O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
: O
Item O
1112 O
( O
b O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

Significant O
Obligors O
of O
Pool O
Assets O
( O
Financial O
Information O
) O
. O

The O
assets O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
include O
a O
collateral O
certificate O
" " O
Series I-MISC
2002-CC I-MISC
( O
the O
First I-MISC
USA I-MISC
Collateral I-MISC
Certificate I-MISC
) O
" " O
representing O
an O
undivided O
interest O
in O
the O
assets O
of O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Credit I-ORG
Card I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
( O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
) O
" " O
whose O
assets O
include O
credit O
card O
receivables O
arising O
in O
consumer O
revolving O
credit O
card O
accounts O
owned O
by O
Chase I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
) O
. O

The O
First I-MISC
USA I-MISC
Collateral I-MISC
Certificate I-MISC
represents O
less O
than O
20 O
% O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
asset O
pool O
. O

The O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
should O
not O
be O
considered O
a O
significant O
obligor O
in O
relation O
to O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
under O
Item O
1112 O
( O
b O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

Nevertheless O
" " O
the O
information O
required O
by O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
for O
an O
asset-backed O
issuer O
in O
respect O
of O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
has O
been O
disclosed O
in O
this O
report O
on O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

The O
assets O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
included O
a O
collateral O
certificate O
" " O
Series I-MISC
2004-CC I-MISC
( O
the O
Chase I-MISC
Collateral I-MISC
Certificate I-MISC
) O
" " O
representing O
an O
undivided O
interest O
in O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Credit I-ORG
Card I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
( O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
) O
" " O
whose O
assets O
included O
credit O
card O
receivables O
arising O
in O
consumer O
revolving O
credit O
card O
accounts O
owned O
by O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
. O

The O
Chase I-MISC
Collateral I-MISC
Certificate I-MISC
was O
paid O
in O
full O
and O
terminated O
on O
December O
15 O
" " O
2009 O
. O

The O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
should O
not O
be O
considered O
a O
significant O
obligor O
in O
relation O
to O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
under O
Item O
1112 O
( O
b O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

Nonetheless O
" " O
the O
information O
required O
by O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
for O
an O
asset-backed O
issuer O
in O
respect O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
has O
been O
disclosed O
in O
this O
report O
on O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

None O
of O
the O
pool O
assets O
held O
by O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
other O
than O
collateral O
certificates O
" " O
and O
none O
of O
the O
pool O
assets O
relating O
to O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
or O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
include O
any O
significant O
obligors O
. O

Item O
1114 O
( O
b O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
of O
Regulation I-MISC
AB I-MISC
: O
Credit O
Enhancement O
and O
Other O
Support O
" " O
Except O
for O
Certain O
Derivatives O
Instruments O
( O
Financial O
Information O
) O
. O

Item O
1115 O
( O
b O
) O
of O
Regulation I-MISC
AB I-MISC
: O
Certain O
Derivatives O
Instruments O
( O
Financial O
Information O
) O
. O

Item O
1117 O
of O
Regulation I-MISC
AB I-MISC
: O
Legal O
Proceedings O
. O

The O
action O
asserted O
that O
the O
rules O
of O
the O
foregoing O
associations O
regarding O
the O
uniform O
acceptance O
of O
all O
VISA I-ORG
and O
MasterCard I-ORG
cards O
" " O
including O
debit O
VISA I-ORG
and O
MasterCard I-ORG
cards O
" " O
constituted O
an O
illegal O
tying O
arrangement O
. O

In O
April O
2003 O
" " O
MasterCard I-ORG
and O
VISA I-ORG
each O
agreed O
to O
settle O
the O
matter O
by O
among O
other O
things O
" " O
reducing O
interchange O
rates O
for O
debit O
cards O
" " O
allowing O
merchants O
to O
decline O
debit O
cards O
" " O
and O
agreeing O
to O
pay O
into O
settlement O
funds O
as O
follows O
: O
MasterCard I-ORG
agreed O
to O
pay O
into O
a O
settlement O
fund O
approximately O
$ O
1 O
billion O
over O
ten O
years O
and O
VISA I-ORG
agreed O
to O
pay O
approximately O
$ O
2 O
billion O
over O
ten O
years O
. O

On O
December O
19 O
" " O
2003 O
" " O
the O
District O
Court O
granted O
final O
approval O
of O
the O
settlement O
. O

The O
court O
interpreted O
the O
release O
provided O
by O
the O
merchant O
class O
as O
encompassing O
any O
possible O
suit O
by O
class O
members O
with O
respect O
to O
debit O
or O
credit O
card O
interchange O
fees O
or O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
exclusionary O
rules O
barring O
issuance O
of O
American I-ORG
Express I-ORG
or O
Discover I-ORG
cards O
by O
member O
banks O
and O
as O
prohibiting O
such O
suits O
against O
the O
member O
banks O
as O
well O
as O
against O
the O
associations O
. O

Certain O
merchants O
that O
had O
previously O
opted O
out O
of O
the O
settlement O
filed O
separate O
lawsuits O
and O
the O
opt O
out O
actions O
have O
been O
resolved O
. O

The O
complaint O
alleges O
that O
VISA I-ORG
" " O
MasterCard I-ORG
and O
certain O
member O
banks O
including O
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
" " O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " O
Capital I-ORG
One I-ORG
" " O
Citibank I-ORG
and O
others O
" " O
conspired O
to O
set O
the O
price O
of O
interchange O
in O
violation O
of O
Section O
1 O
of O
the O
Sherman I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

The O
complaint O
further O
alleges O
tying/bundling O
and O
exclusive O
dealing O
. O

An O
amended O
consolidated O
complaint O
was O
filed O
on O
April O
24 O
" " O
2006 O
. O

The O
consolidated O
complaint O
also O
added O
claims O
relating O
to O
off O
line O
debit O
transactions O
. O

Defendants O
filed O
a O
motion O
to O
dismiss O
all O
claims O
that O
pre-date O
January O
1 O
" " O
2004 O
" " O
based O
on O
the O
settlement O
and O
release O
of O
claims O
in O
the O
Wal-Mart I-ORG
case O
. O

On O
January O
8 O
" " O
2008 O
" " O
the O
Court O
granted O
that O
motion O
and O
those O
claims O
have O
been O
dismissed O
. O

In O
May O
2008 O
" " O
the O
plaintiffs O
filed O
a O
motion O
seeking O
class O
certification O
and O
the O
defendants O
opposed O
that O
motion O
in O
October O
2008 O
. O

The O
court O
has O
not O
yet O
ruled O
on O
the O
class O
certification O
motion O
. O

In O
addition O
to O
the O
consolidated O
class O
action O
complaint O
" " O
plaintiffs O
filed O
supplemental O
complaints O
challenging O
the O
MasterCard I-ORG
and O
Visa I-ORG
initial O
public O
offerings O
( O
each O
" " O
an O
IPO O
) O
. O

With O
respect O
to O
MasterCard I-ORG
" " O
plaintiffs O
first O
filed O
a O
supplemental O
complaint O
in O
May O
2006 O
alleging O
that O
the O
offering O
violated O
Section O
7 O
of O
the O
Clayton I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
Section O
1 O
of O
the O
Sherman I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
and O
that O
the O
offering O
was O
a O
fraudulent O
conveyance O
. O

Defendants O
filed O
a O
motion O
to O
dismiss O
both O
of O
those O
claims O
. O

On O
November O
25 O
" " O
2008 O
" " O
the O
District O
Court O
dismissed O
the O
supplemental O
complaints O
with O
leave O
to O
replead O
. O

In O
January O
2009 O
" " O
the O
plaintiffs O
filed O
and O
served O
a O
Second O
Amended O
Consolidated O
Class O
Action O
Complaint O
against O
all O
defendants O
and O
an O
amended O
supplemental O
complaint O
against O
MasterCard I-ORG
again O
challenging O
the O
MasterCard I-ORG
IPO O
making O
antitrust O
claims O
similar O
to O
those O
that O
were O
set O
forth O
in O
the O
original O
supplemental O
complaint O
" " O
as O
well O
as O
the O
fraudulent O
conveyance O
claim O
. O

With O
respect O
to O
the O
Visa I-ORG
IPO O
" " O
the O
plaintiffs O
filed O
a O
supplemental O
complaint O
challenging O
the O
Visa I-ORG
IPO O
on O
antitrust O
theories O
parallel O
to O
those O
articulated O
in O
the O
MasterCard I-ORG
IPO O
pleading O
. O

On O
March O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
" " O
defendants O
filed O
a O
motion O
to O
dismiss O
the O
Second O
Amended O
Consolidated O
Class O
Action O
Complaint O
. O

Separate O
motions O
to O
dismiss O
each O
of O
the O
supplemental O
complaints O
challenging O
the O
MasterCard I-ORG
and O
Visa I-ORG
IPOs O
were O
also O
filed O
. O

Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
can O
not O
predict O
with O
any O
degree O
of O
certainty O
the O
final O
outcome O
of O
the O
litigation O
described O
above O
" " O
its O
effect O
on O
the O
credit O
card O
industry O
or O
its O
effect O
on O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
s O
credit O
card O
business O
. O

The O
case O
was O
brought O
under O
the O
California I-LOC
unfair O
business O
practices O
statute O
. O

On O
April O
7 O
" " O
2003 O
" " O
the O
court O
issued O
a O
decision O
in O
favor O
of O
the O
plaintiff O
and O
against O
VISA I-ORG
and O
MasterCard I-ORG
" " O
holding O
that O
the O
networks O
disclosures O
of O
the O
1 O
% O
currency O
conversion O
fee O
were O
inadequate O
under O
California I-LOC
law O
. O

VISA I-ORG
and O
MasterCard I-ORG
appealed O
the O
decision O
. O

On O
September O
28 O
" " O
2005 O
" " O
the O
appellate O
court O
reversed O
the O
judgment O
and O
remanded O
the O
case O
to O
the O
trial O
court O
for O
further O
consideration O
. O

The O
reversal O
was O
based O
on O
the O
amendment O
to O
the O
California I-LOC
statute O
at O
issue O
in O
the O
case O
" " O
which O
now O
requires O
the O
plaintiff O
to O
have O
suffered O
actual O
injury O
. O

The O
appellate O
court O
directed O
the O
trial O
court O
to O
exercise O
its O
discretion O
to O
determine O
whether O
to O
grant O
leave O
to O
amend O
the O
complaint O
to O
add O
a O
new O
plaintiff O
. O

Beginning O
in O
or O
around O
February O
2001 O
" " O
more O
than O
twenty O
individual O
credit O
cardholders O
filed O
putative O
class O
actions O
against O
VISA I-ORG
International I-ORG
Service I-ORG
Association I-ORG
" " I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
" " O
VISA I-ORG
U.S.A. I-ORG
" " I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
" " O
MasterCard I-ORG
International I-ORG
Incorporated I-ORG
and O
seven O
credit O
card O
issuing O
banks O
and O
their O
parent O
companies O
" " O
including O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
and O
JPMorgan I-ORG
Chase I-ORG
& I-ORG
Co. I-ORG
" " O
alleging O
that O
VISA I-ORG
and O
MasterCard I-ORG
" " O
together O
with O
their O
members O
banks O
" " O
had O
conspired O
to O
fix O
the O
price O
of O
currency O
conversion O
services O
for O
credit O
card O
purchases O
made O
in O
a O
foreign O
currency O
by O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
cardholders O
. O

The O
plaintiffs O
also O
asserted O
that O
disclosure O
requirements O
of O
the O
Truth-in-Lending I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
and O
regulations O
promulgated O
thereunder O
had O
not O
been O
observed O
. O

On O
July O
3 O
" " O
2003 O
" " O
the O
court O
denied O
in O
principal O
part O
the O
defendants O
motion O
to O
dismiss O
the O
consolidated O
complaint O
. O

On O
November O
12 O
" " O
2003 O
" " O
the O
plaintiffs O
moved O
for O
an O
order O
certifying O
the O
action O
as O
a O
class O
action O
" " O
and O
by O
Order O
dated O
October O
15 O
" " O
2004 O
" " O
the O
court O
granted O
class O
certification O
. O

On O
July O
20 O
" " O
2006 O
" " O
the O
parties O
in O
the O
consolidated O
case O
entered O
into O
a O
nationwide O
settlement O
agreement O
" " O
subject O
to O
court O
approval O
. O

The O
court O
held O
a O
final O
approval O
hearing O
on O
March O
31 O
" " O
2008 O
and O
took O
the O
matter O
under O
advisement O
. O

The O
defendants O
have O
denied O
any O
wrongdoing O
" " O
and O
the O
court O
has O
not O
made O
any O
ruling O
on O
the O
merits O
of O
the O
case O
. O

The O
settlement O
agreement O
includes O
provisions O
relating O
to O
disclosures O
on O
billing O
statements O
and O
other O
documents O
" " O
and O
a O
settlement O
fund O
of O
$ O
"336,000,000" O
to O
pay O
monetary O
claims O
" " O
the O
costs O
of O
administering O
the O
settlement O
and O
notice O
to O
cardholders O
" " O
court-approved O
attorneys O
fees O
and O
expenses O
" " O
and O
court-approved O
awards O
to O
the O
class O
representatives O
. O

Eligible O
cardholders O
will O
be O
able O
to O
make O
monetary O
claims O
. O

The O
settlement O
documents O
include O
agreements O
to O
settle O
certain O
related O
lawsuits O
" " O
including O
the O
lawsuit O
filed O
by O
Adam I-PER
A. I-PER
Schwartz I-PER
against O
the O
VISA I-ORG
and O
MasterCard I-ORG
entities O
as O
referenced O
above O
. O

The O
court O
granted O
final O
approval O
of O
the O
settlement O
on O
October O
22 O
" " O
2009 O
. O

On O
January O
3 O
" " O
2006 O
" " O
plaintiff O
McCoy I-PER
filed O
a O
Second O
Amended O
Complaint O
" " O
alleging O
that O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
violated O
the O
Truth-in-Lending I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
and O
bringing O
state O
law O
claims O
for O
unconscionability O
" " O
declaratory O
relief O
" " O
illegal O
penalty O
" " O
consumer O
fraud O
" " O
breach O
of O
contract O
and O
breach O
of O
the O
implied O
covenant O
of O
good O
faith O
and O
fair O
dealing O
. O

Plaintiff O
brought O
suit O
on O
behalf O
of O
a O
putative O
class O
of O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
credit O
card O
customers O
who O
claim O
that O
their O
interest O
rates O
were O
increased O
without O
notice O
after O
they O
made O
a O
late O
payment O
to O
either O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
or O
another O
creditor O
. O

Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
removed O
the O
case O
to O
federal O
court O
and O
then O
moved O
to O
dismiss O
the O
complaint O
. O

On O
August O
21 O
" " O
2006 O
" " O
the O
court O
granted O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
s O
motion O
and O
dismissed O
the O
case O
. O

The O
court O
reversed O
the O
dismissal O
of O
several O
of O
the O
state O
law O
claims O
( O
unconscionability O
" " O
declaratory O
relief O
" " O
illegal O
penalty O
and O
breach O
of O
contract O
) O
and O
remanded O
the O
case O
to O
the O
lower O
court O
. O

Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
can O
not O
predict O
with O
any O
degree O
of O
certainty O
the O
final O
outcome O
of O
the O
litigation O
described O
above O
" " O
its O
effect O
on O
the O
credit O
card O
industry O
or O
its O
effect O
on O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
s O
credit O
card O
business O
. O

A O
number O
of O
lawsuits O
seeking O
class O
action O
certification O
have O
been O
filed O
in O
both O
state O
and O
federal O
courts O
against O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
. O

These O
lawsuits O
challenge O
certain O
policies O
and O
practices O
of O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
s O
credit O
card O
business O
. O

A O
few O
of O
these O
lawsuits O
have O
been O
conditionally O
certified O
as O
class O
actions O
. O

Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
has O
defended O
itself O
against O
claims O
in O
the O
past O
and O
intends O
to O
continue O
to O
do O
so O
in O
the O
future O
. O

While O
it O
is O
impossible O
to O
predict O
the O
outcome O
of O
any O
of O
these O
lawsuits O
" " O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
believes O
that O
any O
liability O
that O
might O
result O
from O
any O
of O
these O
lawsuits O
will O
not O
have O
a O
material O
adverse O
effect O
on O
the O
credit O
card O
receivables O
. O

The O
following O
Items O
have O
been O
omitted O
in O
accordance O
with O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
: O

None O
The O
following O
Items O
have O
been O
omitted O
in O
accordance O
with O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10 I-MISC
K I-MISC
: O

Substitute O
information O
provided O
in O
accordance O
with O
General O
Instruction O
J O
to O
Form I-MISC
10 I-MISC
K I-MISC
: O
Item O
1119 O
of O
Regulation I-MISC
AB I-MISC
: O
Affiliations O
and O
Certain O
Relationships O
and O
Related O
Transactions O
. O

Information O
required O
by O
Item O
1119 O
of O
Regulation I-MISC
AB I-MISC
has O
been O
omitted O
from O
this O
report O
on O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
in O
reliance O
on O
the O
Instruction O
to O
Item O
1119 O
. O

Each O
of O
Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " O
as O
the O
servicer O
for O
each O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
" " O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
and O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
" " O
and O
BNY I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
" " O
as O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
trustee O
" " O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
" " O
as O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
trustee O
and O
Wells I-ORG
Fargo I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
Wells I-ORG
Fargo I-ORG
) O
" " O
as O
the O
indenture O
trustee O
for O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
( O
each O
" " O
a O
Servicing O
Participant O
) O
was O
a O
party O
participating O
in O
the O
servicing O
function O
during O
the O
reporting O
period O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
pool O
assets O
held O
by O
the O
respective O
trust O
. O

Assessment O
are O
attached O
as O
exhibits O
to O
this O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

In O
addition O
" " O
each O
of O
the O
Servicing O
Participants O
has O
provided O
an O
attestation O
report O
( O
each O
" " O
an O
Attestation O
Report O
) O
by O
a O
registered O
independent O
public O
accounting O
firm O
regarding O
its O
related O
Report O
on O
Assessment O
. O

Each O
Attestation O
Report O
is O
attached O
as O
an O
exhibit O
to O
this O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

Item O
1123 O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
: O
Servicer O
Compliance O
Statement O
. O

Chase I-ORG
USA I-ORG
is O
the O
servicer O
and O
has O
provided O
a O
statement O
of O
compliance O
( O
a O
Compliance O
Statement O
) O
for O
the O
period O
from O
and O
including O
January O
1 O
" " O
2009 O
through O
and O
including O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
for O
each O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
" " O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
and O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
. O

Each O
such O
Compliance O
Statement O
has O
been O
signed O
by O
an O
authorized O
officer O
of O
the O
servicer O
for O
the O
respective O
issuing O
entity O
and O
is O
attached O
as O
an O
exhibit O
to O
this O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

None O
of O
the O
Reports O
on O
Assessment O
or O
the O
related O
Attestation O
Reports O
has O
identified O
any O
material O
instances O
of O
noncompliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
described O
in O
the O
related O
Report O
on O
Assessment O
as O
being O
applicable O
to O
such O
Servicing O
Participant O
except O
that O
the O
Report O
on O
Assessment O
provided O
by O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
" " O
BNY I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
and O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
Company I-ORG
" " I-ORG
N.A I-ORG
. I-ORG

( O
collectively O
BNY I-ORG
) O
describes O
a O
material O
instance O
of O
noncompliance O
with O
respect O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
that O
is O
not O
applicable O
to O
any O
of O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Issuance I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
" " O
the O
First I-ORG
USA I-ORG
Credit I-ORG
Card I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
or O
the O
Chase I-ORG
Credit I-ORG
Card I-ORG
Master I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
. O

The O
Report O
on O
Assessment O
provided O
by O
BNY I-ORG
was O
prepared O
on O
a O
platform O
basis O
. O

During O
the O
reporting O
period O
" " O
certain O
payments O
on O
pool O
assets O
were O
not O
deposited O
into O
the O
appropriate O
segregated O
custodial O
bank O
account O
within O
the O
time O
frame O
required O
by O
the O
related O
transaction O
documents O
. O

The O
segregated O
account O
for O
each O
specified O
series O
of O
securities O
was O
in O
existence O
prior O
to O
the O
time O
the O
deposits O
were O
to O
be O
made O
into O
such O
account O
but O
such O
account O
was O
not O
utilized O
in O
all O
instances O
by O
BNY I-ORG
as O
stated O
above O
. O

However O
" " O
payments O
related O
to O
each O
specified O
series O
of O
securities O
were O
timely O
remitted O
to O
the O
investors O
in O
such O
series O
. O

Existing O
procedures O
have O
been O
reviewed O
with O
staff O
to O
enable O
future O
payments O
to O
be O
deposited O
into O
the O
segregated O
account O
for O
each O
specified O
series O
within O
the O
applicable O
time O
frames O
. O

( O
a O
) O
( O
1 O
) O
Not O
Applicable O
. O

( O
a O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
Not O
Applicable O
. O

( O
a O
) O
( O
3 O
) O
See O
Item O
15 O
( O
b O
) O
below O
. O

SUPPLEMENTAL O
INFORMATION O
TO O
BE O
FURNISHED O
WITH O
REPORTS O
FILED O
PURSUANT O
TO O
SECTION O
15 O
( O
d O
) O
OF O
THE O
ACT O
BY O
REGISTRANTS O
WHICH O
HAVE O
NOT O
REGISTERED O
SECURITIES O
PURSUANT O
TO O
SECTION O
12 O
OF O
THE O
ACT O
. O

No O
annual O
report O
to O
security O
holders O
or O
proxy O
statement O
" " O
form O
of O
proxy O
or O
other O
proxy O
soliciting O
material O
has O
been O
sent O
to O
security O
holders O
or O
is O
anticipated O
to O
be O
furnished O
to O
security O
holders O
subsequent O
to O
the O
filing O
of O
this O
annual O
report O
on O
Form I-MISC
10-K I-MISC
. O

CHASE I-ORG
ISSUANCE I-ORG
TRUST/ I-ORG
FIRST B-ORG
USA I-ORG
CREDIT I-ORG
CARD I-ORG
MASTER I-ORG
TRUST/ I-ORG
CHASE B-ORG
CREDIT I-ORG
CARD I-ORG
MASTER I-ORG
TRUST I-ORG
( O
Issuing O
entities O
) O

CHASE I-ORG
BANK I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " I-ORG
NATIONAL I-ORG
ASSOCIATION I-ORG
" " O

( O
senior O
officer O
of O
Chase I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
in O
charge O
of O
securitization O
) O

Exhibit O
31.1 O
Exhibit O
31.1 O
I O
" " O
Keith I-PER
W. I-PER
Schuck I-PER
" " O
certify O
that O
: O

In O
giving O
the O
certification O
above O
" " O
I O
have O
reasonably O
relied O
on O
information O
provided O
to O
me O
by O
the O
following O
unaffiliated O
parties O
: O
BNY I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
" " O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
" " O
Wilmington I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
Company I-ORG
and O
Wells I-ORG
Fargo I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
. O

( O
senior O
officer O
of O
Chase I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
in O
charge O
of O
securitization O
) O

Class O
A O
( O
2002-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2003-4 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2003-8 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2004-1 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2004-3 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2004-5 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2004-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2004-7 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2004-8 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-2 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-3 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-4 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-5 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-7 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-8 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-9 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-10 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-11 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2005-13 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-1 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-2 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-3 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-4 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-5 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-7 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2006-8 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-1 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-2 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-3 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-4 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-5 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-7 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-8 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-9 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-10 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-11 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-12 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-13 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-14 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-15 O
) O

Class O
A O
( O
2007-16 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-17 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2007-18 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-1 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-2 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-3 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-4 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-5 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-7 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-8 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-9 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-10 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-11 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-12 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-13 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2008-14 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-2 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-3 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-4 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-5 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-6 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-7 O
) O
Class O
A O
( O
2009-8 O
) O
Class O
B O
( O
2004-01 O
) O
Class O
B O
( O
2004-02 O
) O
Class O
B O
( O
2006-01 O
) O
Class O
B O
( O
2006-02 O
) O
Class O
B O
( O
2007-01 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2003-03 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2004-01 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2004-02 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2004-03 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2005-01 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2005-02 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2005-03 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2006-02 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2006-03 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2006-04 O
) O
Class O
C O
( O
2007-01 O
) O

Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
: O
All O
servicing O
criteria O
set O
forth O
in O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
" " O
to O
the O
extent O
required O
in O
the O
related O
transaction O
agreements O
" " O
or O
required O
by O
the O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
servicing O
criteria O
in O
regards O
to O
the O
activities O
performed O
by O
the O
Company O
" " O
except O
for O
the O
following O
criteria O
: O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
ii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
iv O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
v O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
viii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
ix O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
x O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xi O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xii O
) O
and O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xiii O
) O
" " O
which O
Management O
has O
determined O
are O
not O
applicable O
to O
the O
activities O
the O
Company O
performs O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Platform O
( O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
) O
. O

Period O
: O
As O
of O
and O
for O
the O
twelve O
months O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
( O
the O
Period O
) O
. O

Third O
parties O
classified O
as O
vendors O
: O
With O
respect O
to O
servicing O
criteria O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
engaged O
various O
vendors O
to O
handle O
certain O
Uniform O
Commercial O
Code O
filing O
functions O
required O
by O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
( O
vendors O
) O
. O

The O
Company O
has O
determined O
that O
none O
of O
these O
vendors O
are O
a O
servicer O
as O
defined O
in O
Item O
1101 O
( O
j O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
and O
the O
Company O
elects O
to O
take O
responsibility O
for O
assessing O
compliance O
with O
the O
portion O
of O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
applicable O
to O
each O
vendor O
as O
permitted O
by O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
of O
the O
SEC I-GOVERNMENT
Division I-GOVERNMENT
of I-GOVERNMENT
Corporation I-GOVERNMENT
Finance I-GOVERNMENT
Manual B-LEGISLATION/ACT
of I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Publicly I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Available I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Telephone I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Interpretations I-LEGISLATION/ACT
( O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
) O
. O

The O
Company O
has O
policies O
and O
procedures O
in O
place O
to O
provide O
reasonable O
assurance O
that O
the O
vendor O
s O
activities O
comply O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
applicable O
to O
each O
vendor O
. O

The O
Company O
is O
solely O
responsible O
for O
determining O
that O
it O
meets O
the O
SEC I-GOVERNMENT
requirements O
to O
apply O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
for O
the O
vendors O
and O
related O
criteria O
. O

With O
respect O
to O
the O
Platform O
and O
the O
Period O
" " O
the O
Company O
provides O
the O
following O
assessment O
of O
compliance O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
: O
1 O
. O

The O
Company O
is O
responsible O
for O
assessing O
its O
compliance O
with O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
. O

The O
Company O
has O
assessed O
compliance O
with O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
" " O
including O
servicing O
criteria O
for O
which O
compliance O
is O
determined O
based O
on O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
as O
described O
above O
" " O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
Period O
. O

In O
performing O
this O
assessment O
" " O
management O
used O
the O
criteria O
set O
forth O
by O
the O
Securities I-GOVERNMENT
and I-GOVERNMENT
Exchange I-GOVERNMENT
Commission I-GOVERNMENT
in O
paragraph O
( O
d O
) O
of O
Item O
1122 O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

Based O
on O
such O
assessment O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
Period O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
complied O
" " O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
with O
the O
applicable O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

KPMG I-ORG
LLP I-ORG
" " O
a O
registered O
public O
accounting O
firm O
" " O
has O
issued O
an O
attestation O
report O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
assessment O
of O
compliance O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
Period O
. O

The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
( O
formerly O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
) O
" " O
BNY I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
( O
formerly O
BNYM I-ORG
( I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
) I-ORG
) O
and O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
Company I-ORG
" " I-ORG
N.A I-ORG
. I-ORG

( O
formerly O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
Company I-ORG
" " I-ORG
N.A I-ORG
. I-ORG

) O
" " O
( O
collectively O
" " O
the O
Company O
) O
provides O
this O
platform-level O
assessment O
of O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
specified O
in O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
promulgated O
by O
the O
Securities I-GOVERNMENT
and I-GOVERNMENT
Exchange I-GOVERNMENT
Commission I-GOVERNMENT
. O

Management O
has O
determined O
that O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
are O
applicable O
in O
regard O
to O
the O
servicing O
platform O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
period O
as O
follows O
: O
Platform O
: O
Publicly-issued O
( O
i.e. O
" " O
transaction-level O
reporting O
initially O
required O
under O
the O
Securities I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Exchange I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
of I-LEGISLATION/ACT
1934 I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
as O
amended O
) O
asset-backed O
securities O
issued O
on O
or O
after O
January O
1 O
" " O
2006 O
and O
like-kind O
transactions O
issued O
prior O
to O
January O
1 O
" " O
2006 O
that O
comply O
with O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
for O
which O
the O
Company O
provides O
trustee O
" " O
securities O
administration O
or O
paying O
agent O
services O
" " O
as O
defined O
and O
to O
the O
extent O
applicable O
in O
the O
transaction O
agreements O
" " O
other O
than O
residential O
mortgage-backed O
securities O
and O
other O
mortgage-related O
asset-backed O
securities O
. O

Period O
: O
Twelve O
months O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
( O
the O
Period O
) O
. O

Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
: O
All O
servicing O
criteria O
set O
forth O
in O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
" " O
to O
the O
extent O
required O
by O
the O
related O
transaction O
agreements O
as O
to O
any O
transaction O
" " O
except O
as O
set O
forth O
in O
the O
column O
titled O
Not O
Applicable O
To O
Platform O
in O
Appendix O
1 O
attached O
hereto O
. O

With O
respect O
to O
applicable O
servicing O
criteria O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
iii O
) O
and O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
vii O
) O
" " O
there O
were O
no O
activities O
performed O
during O
the O
Period O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Platform O
" " O
because O
there O
were O
no O
occurrences O
of O
events O
that O
would O
require O
the O
Company O
to O
perform O
such O
activities O
. O

With O
respect O
to O
servicing O
criteria O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
vi O
) O
management O
has O
engaged O
a O
vendor O
to O
perform O
the O
activities O
required O
by O
these O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

Management O
has O
determined O
that O
this O
vendor O
is O
not O
considered O
a O
servicer O
as O
defined O
in O
Item O
1101 O
( O
j O
) O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
and O
management O
has O
elected O
to O
take O
responsibility O
for O
assessing O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
applicable O
to O
this O
vendor O
as O
permitted O
by O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
of O
the O
SEC I-GOVERNMENT
Division I-GOVERNMENT
of I-GOVERNMENT
Corporation I-GOVERNMENT
Finance I-GOVERNMENT
Manual B-LEGISLATION/ACT
of I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Publicly I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Available I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Telephone I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Interpretations I-LEGISLATION/ACT
( O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
) O
. O

Management O
has O
policies O
and O
procedures O
in O
place O
designed O
to O
provide O
reasonable O
assurance O
that O
the O
vendor O
s O
activities O
comply O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
applicable O
to O
the O
vendor O
. O

Management O
is O
solely O
responsible O
for O
determining O
that O
it O
meets O
the O
SEC I-GOVERNMENT
requirements O
to O
apply O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
for O
the O
vendor O
and O
related O
criteria O
. O

With O
respect O
to O
the O
Platform O
and O
the O
Period O
" " O
the O
Company O
provides O
the O
following O
assessment O
of O
compliance O
in O
respect O
of O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
: O
1 O
. O

The O
Company O
is O
responsible O
for O
assessing O
its O
compliance O
with O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
. O

The O
Company O
has O
assessed O
compliance O
with O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
including O
servicing O
criteria O
for O
which O
compliance O
is O
determined O
based O
on O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
as O
described O
above O
. O

In O
performing O
this O
assessment O
" " O
management O
used O
the O
criteria O
set O
forth O
by O
the O
Securities I-GOVERNMENT
and I-GOVERNMENT
Exchange I-GOVERNMENT
Commission I-GOVERNMENT
in O
paragraph O
( O
d O
) O
of O
Item O
1122 O
of O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
. O

Based O
on O
such O
assessment O
" " O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
Period O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
complied O
" " O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
" " O
with O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
other O
than O
as O
identified O
on O
Schedule O
A O
attached O
. O

KPMG I-ORG
LLP I-ORG
" " O
an O
independent O
registered O
public O
accounting O
firm O
" " O
has O
issued O
an O
attestation O
report O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
Period O
. O

1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
: O
Payments O
on O
pool O
assets O
are O
deposited O
into O
the O
appropriate O
custodial O
bank O
accounts O
and O
related O
bank O
clearing O
accounts O
no O
more O
than O
two O
business O
days O
of O
receipt O
" " O
or O
such O
other O
number O
of O
days O
specified O
in O
the O
transaction O
agreements O
. O

During O
the O
reporting O
period O
" " O
certain O
payments O
on O
pool O
assets O
were O
not O
deposited O
into O
the O
appropriate O
segregated O
custodial O
bank O
account O
within O
the O
time O
frame O
required O
by O
the O
related O
transaction O
documents O
. O

The O
segregated O
account O
for O
each O
specified O
series O
of O
securities O
was O
in O
existence O
prior O
to O
the O
time O
the O
deposits O
were O
to O
be O
made O
into O
such O
account O
but O
such O
account O
was O
not O
utilized O
in O
all O
instances O
by O
the O
Trustee O
as O
stated O
above O
. O

However O
" " O
payments O
related O
to O
each O
specified O
series O
of O
securities O
were O
timely O
remitted O
to O
the O
investors O
in O
such O
series O
. O

Existing O
procedures O
have O
been O
reviewed O
with O
staff O
to O
enable O
future O
payments O
to O
be O
deposited O
into O
the O
segregated O
account O
for O
each O
specified O
series O
within O
the O
applicable O
time O
frames O
. O

To O
the O
Stockholder O
of O
Chase I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
: O
We O
have O
examined O
Chase I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
USA I-ORG
" " I-ORG
National I-ORG
Association I-ORG
s O
( O
the O
Bank O
) O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
set O
forth O
in O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
of O
the O
Securities I-GOVERNMENT
and I-GOVERNMENT
Exchange I-GOVERNMENT
Commission I-GOVERNMENT
s O
Regulation I-LEGISLATION/ACT
AB I-LEGISLATION/ACT
for O
the O
asset-backed O
securities O
transactions O
for O
which O
the O
Bank O
performed O
servicing O
functions O
set O
forth O
in O
Item O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
involving O
credit O
card O
receivables O
" " O
for O
which O
transactions O
the O
Bank O
acted O
as O
servicer O
" " O
that O
were O
registered O
with O
the O
Securities I-GOVERNMENT
and I-GOVERNMENT
Exchange I-GOVERNMENT
Commission I-GOVERNMENT
pursuant O
to O
the O
Securities I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Act I-LEGISLATION/ACT
of I-LEGISLATION/ACT
1933 I-LEGISLATION/ACT
" " O
as O
amended O
" " O
on O
or O
after O
January O
1 O
" " O
2006 O
" " O
where O
the O
related O
asset-backed O
securities O
were O
outstanding O
( O
the O
Platform O
) O
described O
in O
the O
accompanying O
Management O
s O
Report O
on O
Assessment O
of O
Compliance O
with O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
year O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
" " O
excluding O
criteria O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
1 O
) O
( O
ii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
1 O
) O
( O
iii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
iii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
2 O
) O
( O
iv O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
3 O
) O
( O
iii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
ii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
x O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xi O
) O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xii O
) O
" " O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xiii O
) O
" " O
and O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
xv O
) O
" " O
which O
the O
Bank O
has O
determined O
are O
not O
applicable O
to O
the O
activities O
performed O
by O
it O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Platform O
. O

Exhibit O
B O
to O
management O
s O
assertion O
identifies O
the O
individual O
asset-backed O
transactions O
and O
securities O
defined O
by O
management O
as O
constituting O
the O
Platform O
. O

Management O
is O
responsible O
for O
the O
Bank O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

Our O
responsibility O
is O
to O
express O
an O
opinion O
on O
the O
Bank O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
based O
on O
our O
examination O
. O

Our O
examination O
was O
conducted O
in O
accordance O
with O
attestation O
standards O
of O
the O
Public I-GOVERNMENT
Company I-GOVERNMENT
Accounting I-GOVERNMENT
Oversight I-GOVERNMENT
Board I-GOVERNMENT
( I-GOVERNMENT
United I-GOVERNMENT
States I-GOVERNMENT
) I-GOVERNMENT
and O
" " O
accordingly O
" " O
included O
examining O
" " O
on O
a O
test O
basis O
" " O
evidence O
about O
the O
Bank O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
applicable O
servicing O
criteria O
and O
performing O
such O
other O
procedures O
as O
we O
considered O
necessary O
in O
the O
circumstances O
. O

Our O
examination O
included O
testing O
of O
selected O
asset-backed O
transactions O
and O
securities O
that O
comprise O
the O
Platform O
" " O
testing O
of O
selected O
servicing O
activities O
related O
to O
the O
Platform O
" " O
and O
determining O
whether O
the O
Bank O
processed O
those O
selected O
transactions O
and O
performed O
those O
selected O
activities O
in O
compliance O
with O
the O
applicable O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

Our O
procedures O
were O
limited O
to O
the O
selected O
transactions O
and O
servicing O
activities O
performed O
by O
the O
Bank O
during O
the O
period O
covered O
by O
this O
report O
. O

Our O
procedures O
were O
not O
designed O
to O
detect O
noncompliance O
arising O
from O
errors O
that O
may O
have O
occurred O
prior O
to O
or O
subsequent O
to O
our O
tests O
that O
may O
have O
affected O
the O
balances O
or O
amounts O
calculated O
or O
reported O
by O
the O
Bank O
during O
the O
period O
covered O
by O
this O
report O
. O

We O
believe O
that O
our O
examination O
provides O
a O
reasonable O
basis O
for O
our O
opinion O
. O

Our O
examination O
does O
not O
provide O
a O
legal O
determination O
on O
the O
Bank O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

In O
our O
opinion O
" " O
the O
Bank O
complied O
with O
the O
aforementioned O
applicable O
servicing O
criteria O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
year O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
for O
the O
Platform O
" " O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
. O

Management O
is O
responsible O
for O
the O
Company O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

Our O
responsibility O
is O
to O
express O
an O
opinion O
on O
management O
s O
assessment O
about O
the O
Company O
s O
compliance O
based O
on O
our O
examination O
. O

Our O
examination O
was O
conducted O
in O
accordance O
with O
the O
standards O
of O
the O
Public I-GOVERNMENT
Company I-GOVERNMENT
Accounting I-GOVERNMENT
Oversight I-GOVERNMENT
Board I-GOVERNMENT
( I-GOVERNMENT
United I-GOVERNMENT
States I-GOVERNMENT
) I-GOVERNMENT
and O
" " O
accordingly O
" " O
included O
examining O
" " O
on O
a O
test O
basis O
" " O
evidence O
about O
the O
Company O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
specified O
above O
and O
performing O
such O
other O
procedures O
as O
we O
considered O
necessary O
in O
the O
circumstances O
. O

Our O
examination O
included O
testing O
selected O
asset-backed O
transactions O
and O
securities O
that O
comprise O
the O
Platform O
" " O
testing O
selected O
servicing O
activities O
related O
to O
the O
Platform O
" " O
and O
determining O
whether O
the O
Company O
processed O
those O
selected O
transactions O
and O
performed O
those O
selected O
activities O
in O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

Furthermore O
" " O
our O
procedures O
were O
limited O
to O
the O
selected O
transactions O
and O
servicing O
activities O
performed O
by O
the O
Company O
during O
the O
period O
covered O
by O
this O
report O
. O

Our O
procedures O
were O
not O
designed O
to O
determine O
whether O
errors O
may O
have O
occurred O
either O
prior O
to O
or O
subsequent O
to O
our O
tests O
that O
may O
have O
affected O
the O
balances O
or O
amounts O
calculated O
or O
reported O
by O
the O
Company O
during O
the O
period O
covered O
by O
this O
report O
for O
the O
selected O
transactions O
or O
any O
other O
transactions O
. O

We O
believe O
that O
our O
examination O
provides O
a O
reasonable O
basis O
for O
our O
opinion O
. O

Our O
examination O
does O
not O
provide O
a O
legal O
determination O
on O
the O
Company O
s O
compliance O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

As O
described O
in O
the O
accompanying O
management O
s O
Assessment O
of O
Compliance O
With O
Applicable O
Servicing O
Criteria O
" " O
for O
servicing O
criteria O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
engaged O
a O
vendor O
to O
perform O
the O
activities O
required O
by O
these O
servicing O
criteria O
. O

17.06 O
of O
the O
SEC I-GOVERNMENT
Division I-GOVERNMENT
of I-GOVERNMENT
Corporation I-GOVERNMENT
Finance I-GOVERNMENT
Manual B-LEGISLATION/ACT
of I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Publicly I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Available I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Telephone I-LEGISLATION/ACT
Interpretations I-LEGISLATION/ACT
( O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
) O
. O

As O
permitted O
by O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
" " O
the O
Company O
has O
asserted O
that O
it O
has O
policies O
and O
procedures O
in O
place O
designed O
to O
provide O
reasonable O
assurance O
that O
the O
vendor O
s O
activities O
comply O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
with O
the O
servicing O
criteria O
applicable O
to O
each O
vendor O
. O

The O
Company O
is O
solely O
responsible O
for O
determining O
that O
it O
meets O
the O
SEC I-GOVERNMENT
requirements O
to O
apply O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
for O
the O
vendor O
and O
related O
criteria O
as O
described O
in O
its O
assertion O
" " O
and O
we O
performed O
no O
procedures O
with O
respect O
to O
the O
Company O
s O
eligibility O
to O
apply O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
. O

In O
our O
opinion O
" " O
management O
s O
assessment O
that O
the O
Company O
complied O
with O
the O
aforementioned O
servicing O
criteria O
" " O
including O
servicing O
criteria O
1122 O
( O
d O
) O
( O
4 O
) O
( O
i O
) O
for O
which O
compliance O
is O
determined O
based O
on O
Interpretation O
17.06 O
as O
described O
above O
" " O
as O
of O
and O
for O
the O
twelve O
months O
ended O
December O
31 O
" " O
2009 O
is O
fairly O
stated O
" " O
in O
all O
material O
respects O
. O

The O
Board O
of O
Directors O
The I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
BNY B-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
of I-ORG
Delaware I-ORG
The B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
York I-ORG
Mellon I-ORG
Trust I-ORG
Company I-ORG
" " I-ORG
N.A I-ORG
. I-ORG
